Set all your halos at the gate
Lay down your lilies till you fade
I left a siddle in the dark
Beneath the floorboards of your heart
Till every ghost I never fled
I lay my candle with the day
I am the breath behind the veil
The ocean sang
move through shadow though myself no quiet no crown no help the cold night keeps its watch on
me a black flame burns where light should be and when the world forgets my face i
This is what your needle black flame burns
We're like
Had to delete it anyway. Yeah, why'd you show me the mushroom? Thank you Ray. I'm thank you Ray, and I appreciate that
Yeah, thank you. Hey, I also you guys you're gonna love this one. I did anyone of KZ. I made a video and even RG said
Hey, you're gonna talented there. Hold on. Let's look at the one I did of KZ
It's going on this can't be real get away from me. I don't understand any of this. I
Thought it was pretty good
Hi, hi guys. Wow. Yeah, so Stig is a trans. He actually uses Samoan woman
I always had I always was like he reminds me of a Samoan woman and now I'm you know, he is
Yeah, actually, oh also if um if KZ was a puppet because I'm thinking of either doing a puppet show or a cartoon with
KZ because he was like he's he's you know, he said some terrible things about me
So but he wants to show for he wants to show so this is a
Yeah, this is yeah, that was that was a video. Well, it's not this how about this one
She's had a similar name, like similar name.
Because you can't have the exact same name.
So you're putting like an area or something.
That won't catch the eye, you know, right away.
That's right, you always double check.
Broadway, public transport, and bus connection.
Stop requested.
No angle is good every angle is worse than the previous one. I mean please stop showing me angles
I want to just show me the angle of the camera face facing away from you
Okay, unless it's one of my I'm gonna do a puppet show with okay. See here. It is. This is the puppet show. I'm designing
Closer come closer. Yeah, gotcha
That one's frightening that one's right
And I did those, I made those.
But yeah, but he said some horrible things about me.
He's like, oh, it's the guys.
When KZ is making fun of me,
I think it's just time for me to go.
He was like, oh, Psyche, you're 140 pounds and six foot three.
I think he said six two,
because he knows I said six three,
but I think he's like six two.
And so he can't have me being taller than him
because he gets really insecure about that for some reason.
Looks like, yeah, I mean, yeah, that was kind of the Grinch.
And then so, and then he's like, oh, well,
Oh, and all you eat is McDonald's.
Hey, fucking McDonald's is fucking.
All he does is take a shower at McDonald's.
I mean, at least I mean, we're getting a good coffee.
I mean, I don't know.
I don't wanna make fun of him,
but he's making fun of me.
It's so cruel.
And then he said stuff like I'm on meth and stuff like that.
Well, look at my teeth.
Let's put our teeth together, KZ, KZ.
I know they're not, they're not like perfectly white, right?
I mean, yours look like, like a human rat.
I mean, it's like, yeah, the rat king.
Like, who was the rat king?
I don't know.
What was it?
A shredder from a Ninja Turtles, not shredder.
Splinter, Splinter was the rat, right?
I mean, in his face looks like the member of that giant brain with the intestines, not
for a million dollars bedpan, well maybe for a million dollars, but not for a hundred
thousand, no less than five hundred thousand.
I'll do it for one hundred thousand one dollars.
Okay, never mind, never mind.
Never mind.
Hi, what?
Oh, I'm sorry.
Why, why is he making, it's just, I've had enough.
Look, I mean, look, this is him, literally.
He's going on!
This can't be real!
Get away from me!
I don't understand any of this!
Look how good I got his teeth, though.
I got his teeth perfect.
Yeah.
I mean, when I started my show, like, I had some good pictures, like they showed a good
picture on Samans, but it's like, then they showed like, oh, like, of course I have bad
pictures too.
They had a picture of me, like, I had like, I was eating something, and it's like my teeth
and like, they're falling out of my mouth.
Everyone was like, oh, what, he doesn't have teeth, he has dentures and stuff, it's just
like, it's so fake.
oh and then it's like my neck I was like swallowing something oh look how disgusting his neck is and
I was like sitting there like eating like the most awkward like like this is a worst picture right
it's like that's the one you chose I mean it's like can you use these pink and other like just
picture me like smiling like that'd be like put that next to it and then you can see I don't look
I mean, it's like, yeah, you can find bad angles.
You know, when you like have pictures
and you can find a bad angle, like when you go,
oh, it's like a terrible angle and it looks terrible?
That's all they did.
I mean, it's like, I'm not perfect.
Yeah, they love the bad angle pictures.
Yes, I'll put them in there.
Oh, there was like, oh yeah, oh he had too many fish tacos.
No, I had too much, Bita and Alexandra.
But that's what, they did that to me, not fish tacos.
The fish tacos gave me some nourishment.
I mean, Jesus, cry many.
Nah, I'm just kidding, Bita and Alexandra.
Oh my God, I'm not really, I mean, geez.
Oh, he has like three Adam's apples. No, I have one huge Adam's apple. It looks like a cat's face or an alien or something
I mean, no, it's big. He's a man. Okay. The man. It means I took a big big old bite of the apple and I was choked on it
Yeah, we saw six we everyone saw six vagina
Everyone saw six vagina. I saw it. Chanel and I saw it twice today actually because he did that earlier on
on Bita's show.
I think it was on Bita's.
He would do it on another show.
But I literally thought I was like,
oh, who's the woman?
I said, did Bita drop her camera again?
No, no, I'm just kidding.
I was like, but who's that?
What's that, like the large hairy vagina?
And then Kate said, oh, that's sick.
He poured him out.
I'm like, I didn't know sick was a woman.
Wow, and then did you see the thumbnail? That's one of his bed. That's what the thumbnail is one of his best pictures
That's the wrong link. I don't know. I only have one link. Let me see
post
It opposed my video or something. It was the link. I post. Oh
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay
What was the link I posted? Hopefully it wasn't bad
Subscribe to SIG!
You're such a traitor, Nick. I mean it's like Nick, I have such high hopes for you.
First he tells,
finally after like six months and somebody asked me for a reading the other day,
and then I fell asleep, and then she goes, oh, and I said, but I had told her,
oh, you can go to my, you just write my email and we can work with something out, and she said,
oh, how much is the reading? Two of my mods said,
$9,000 and then the ladies the ladies said, okay, thanks, you know, and never heard from her
You're you're my mom you're my mod now you owe me $9,000 Nick
Until you until then you're never getting up here again
Psyche, you're gonna stop Trosity's fucking clowns,
they whip out their fucking belly buttons, bro.
Well, I had to delete it anyway,
cause I played Alexander's clips and you know,
she clip, she, I'm struck me twice and so.
That's fucking hilarious, bro.
I'm like, dude, what the fuck?
Yeah, I know I'm a high, I'm not that high-end.
I do it for $9, like really, you know, it's like,
I mean, it depends on their budget and stuff.
It begins at $9,000 to scare them away.
Dude, but the ladies in the chat are fucking loving this shit. They're laughing at this fucking this guy whipping out his extra belly button
I fucking
You can donate to my cash app or become a member of the show guys, you know
I don't know how much longer. I'll be on this. I mean my strikes were taken down
But I don't know like I'm being both of them threatened legal action on me
Instead of be to be just that I'm perjuring myself for some reason and then and then Alexander's said I'll you know
See you in court for
for slander like not like she's not there it's queen of slander i mean it's like she i mean
she's telling people people have sex with dogs i mean without proof and stuff like that i mean
it's like jesus crimony oh my god fucking bestiality that's fucking nuts spiritual traffickers who is
Venmo or that, or you can just, well, I'm still monetized.
She runs everyone's, I know, but she slanders.
Isn't she like the worst slander ever?
I mean, it's like, she has literally websites called,
you know, most of Bobby files of, oh, sorry, sorry, shit.
Now I'm in trouble.
Fuck, that was, that was a, you know,
that's very common name in Yvonne.
Sticks on up here.
And also, you know, we know some of the other, you know,
Blogger's butthole or whatever. I don't know. He's not backstage. He's not backstage beanie
Slaughter's butthole. What the fuck blogger's butthole. Oh
Yeah, and she what and she says I'm straight which is straight slander against a gay person
Cuz I'm a gay person and then she said I'm a stalker. She said I'm a spiritual trafficker
She said I'm a fake psychic. Those are all slanderous. I was much nicer to her
I mean, jeez, remember that YouTube creates demons out of you
Creates I mean, she's I think she's a queen of hell
Creates
Geez
She's told me she was a 9,000 year old vampire dinner. I thought she was kidding
Now I don't there. She didn't give you a sake sake. I
Didn't want a sake sake. I'm like I said, I'm not straight. I'm a gay guy
I had enough when I fingered my ex-girlfriend.
I had enough pee, whatever it was.
It was pee or just-
What the fuck is Alice?
Get his fucking ass up here.
She thinks I'm a straight because of my obsession
with women like Bita and Emma.
Yeah, but I'm just very susceptible to succubus energy.
She was a weird alien or a ginger, even worse.
What should I do to succubus?
Yeah, there's succubus. Like I said, I have a tattoo of a succubus on my back. I always have a succubus. I need a succubus in my life.
I feel I have so much spiritual energy. I get overloaded without a succubus taking a lot of it.
Because I'm just able to renew it like Jesus. Like Jesus on the cross. I'm just like the sun.
And I get too intense. I need a succubus to keep me balanced.
Come back
We need to find
She is
beta Lisa
Emma
Alexander they all succubuses
Didn't you know you don't recognize them?
Yeah, and whoever wants to date a ginger only gingers wanted. Oh get the fuck out of here you bitch
Out not allowed in my chat ever out. I
Know she's irreligious, but
That's basically the same as a Satanist. I got you. I got you. I got you Alex
Yeah, and he be let me see Fred Leviathan. That's just Tony. It's always block him. How many people warned you about Alexandra?
probably about
No, I knew it wasn't a happen. I know I'm not I'm not saying I'm surprised. I'm just surprised how like
I'm gonna hire some of these people for psychic readings actually. No, I'm just surprised how like, you know
How it was just like I needed to see it for myself and boy did I find out what did I find out?
I mean, but she would know she really she was so good for like three months
I think she like when her longest like even people were like going back to her because they're like wow she seems cool
Like everyone she I mean she just hated beta and stuff
But I mean everyone else was fine, but it's like now
She'll be cool with me again soon. I hope so. I mean it's like geez I need a
little bit of relief from all this
spiritual energy
Predictable cycle well, so yeah, okay. Well, maybe when I bet when I see her in court
She'll take me to lunch and stuff will be fine after that
She was taking lithium when she was with me and Tommy, but she was just with Tommy last week
I mean, it's like she was just making the junkie jams, you know theme song
I mean, it's like, they're in a convertible.
He was just muscular and he looked great.
I mean, he looked great.
He looked better than I do in that picture that Easymade.
I was like, Tommy and Jake,
oh, and then they're making love
and he has all these freckles on his.
What's that about?
I mean, just like, I don't,
and then she was like, oh, she was like,
oh, I'm exploring the world of gingers.
I think they're like special alien people and stuff.
And I was like, okay.
Ginger's ginger. Yeah, right because Tommy's a ginger. Oh Tommy's a ginger. Hmm, and she's gonna make some ginger bacon jam
Yeah, do you hear and how about this one?
Rain falls down
And she's making fun of my AI
You know what she likes before now. She's now. She's seeing rain falls down and Tommy's like, you know, my girl
It's like it's like the worst rapping and singing I've ever heard of my life, but okay
Tommy might fall in love with ghost. I don't want to be mean. I don't want to be mean. That was yeah
I don't want to be mean. Do you guys did you see I didn't make a video with her? Okay here. Let me just play
I just want to show you I didn't make a this is not like
this is just inspired it's not necessarily this is she's wearing a mask and stuff so you won't see
She needed me for optics, for a sub-block, for a scene
Poking at arrival while pretending to be clean
I thought it was connection, turns out it was theater
A one-woman production call, how can I be meaner?
I was good enough for midnight talks, for spiral rants and victimized
But when the script got rewritten fast, she cut my name from every cat
I was used for till Tuesday
Holy till the fall, then suddenly I'm toxic
The villain after all, don't contact me
She tells me with the curtains dramatic drawn
Then she floats into my panel like a ghost in Mr. Don
Useful to a junior empire
I was there when things were crumbling
Now I'm the big disaster
That's rich coming from the patrons
Ain't a change in every pastor
She found herself a champion
A knight in shining chrome
Posted him like rescue merch
Said finally I'm home
But the armor god did do
Oh you're in it Tommy, you're in it you bitch
Here's time down
Hit the wall, like me
That's your redeemer
Here he is, from A.R.M.A.
He's been there!
Every week a new Messiah
Strat ambassador
Every month a brand new scar
A rotating cast of lifeboats
That don't...
She whispers then appears where I'm live on air like boundaries off of peasants and hypocrisy's couture the way
Now I'm some spiritual trafficker. What a deluxe invention. There's not a charge
It's fan fiction with the persecution pinching
I was there when the wheels came off
Now I'm the dark disaster
That's rich coming from the weather vane
Who calls each storm a pastor
She collects moral costumes
On the stage
Halo for the thumbnail
Pitchfork for the rage
One day you're her confidant
The next day you're her curse
Every friendship gets a trailer
such a beast baby why haunt my little show why bang on the cathedral door you
swore you'd never know don't contact me okay cool her then why are you enrolling
memorizing every word contact me fine by me then why do you keep orbiting my
so-called monstrosity
Who borrowed truth for leverage and performed pain with style
I'll be over here still breathing, still speaking, still
You didn't like it, Tommy?
You didn't like it?
Unfortunately, Tommy, you were in the video.
Suffer and suck-a-tash.
Jesus, cry-mini.
I mean, geez, Tommy, you have to, oh, this sucks.
Really, it did.
If you listened to the lyrics, it was pretty much fucking.
Best lyrics one of my favorite videos ever made Tommy doesn't like it. He can go change the channel
I know you know Tommy goes into mattress stores and harasses
Lady there he's the only customer. She's telling the other customer to call the police is you know
He's running down the street, you know trying to avoid the police and stuff
And then he then he goes and goes into a supermarket and says that the tuna section smells like his ex-girlfriend and stuff
I mean Tommy wait a minute. I thought that Tommy were goes to the Walmart employee
bathroom in the back of me has his own glory hole
Well, he should I mean I bet he does I mean, but I don't know I think his his penis looks like sigs
What with them with them with the ginger with a red wig? I mean, it's terrible and
Tell me I don't know why are you why are you picking on me?
I'm gonna play that you're gonna play your clips again, too. I played them your rumble thing
Oh, yeah, Tripp kick clip you clipped your harassing everywhere in the supermarket. It was really funny actually you guys want to see
Listen
We were asking the supermarket and everyone and like and then they're all calling the cops on him and he's like hey
It means it's like he is pretty funny
This is tripkicks latest video
He put on rumble, but you know, I think that uh
I think you guys will like it here.
Let me just put it on.
This is Tripkicks latest video.
Tommy James, he's got a grocery store
for shops for poopy tuna.
I don't know why it's called poopy tuna.
Poopy tuna.
In the mod, they were joking about pet care
and taking cats to the vet.
That someone from Emma's chat,
she was just thanked one of the mods
and they were joking about pet care and taking,
oh, okay, it's probably KZ.
Or Blade, or Blade, you were spot,
oh, it was you?
Here, watch this one.
In fact, we get peepin', we peep on you, we're peepin'.
Not that Persian style, but on me.
On Nicoletan, peeping top, peeping top.
I'm gonna go to her chat and say hi,
but still my name is different than this.
I might be blocking her chat.
On Nicoletan, son.
We keep on you
Keeping time, keeping time
I'm keeping on
I just wanted to come say hi to you man, and I hope you have a good day. If you're around I'll see you around here
I'm looking for my brother over here. He's small autistic. He gets lost
He's kind of hard to find sometimes, but his name's Sigmund. If you see a little kid brown hair
He's got real big man boobies
If he looks lost maybe just say hey your brother's looking for you stay here Tommy
Oh, mind if I get a hug to smell you a little bit closer. Oh, God
Can I smell you a little closer? What a fucking freak?
Didn't mean to weird you out
Lady where do you work me out?
My cousin touched my wiener
Any
See that's what I mean this guy
Sorry about that
Yeah, I haven't been taking mine
That she's actually knows me and he is spot on he knows when I'm not on my meds, you know that
Ooh
You got tuna here too, huh Bob? Oh
Wow
Whenever you have a minute, I think I kind of know
Whoo, I'm gonna be honest with you real quick. It smells like my ex-girlfriend over here not in a good way
But that's what we're about to see, right?
You know, of course, of course, but I just want to make sure that we're going, getting
the best meat for the best price.
And then every time I keep thinking about the meat, no freaky, I smell that smell and
I'm wondering is that the, is that the product or is that you?
You know what, sir?
At least it isn't poop tuna. I'm gonna let you go about your work and figure out what I want. Apparently. I'm not ready
Yes, sir, I'll be back on the way out. What a great a asshole
Goodies to what you got there some little taters little taters. I know not at all. I'm just looking around still
ask you to leave we can't have you filming in here oh no film I was watching a movie yeah I
can see you filming and we had customers saying that you're seeing profanity to them oh no no
profanity no oh okay that's fine I suppose I suppose I can respect that I didn't take my meds so maybe
get out oh maybe that's why he got mad I don't know out yeah I'll just walk out it's not a big deal
It's not like I'm having a psychotic episode or anything.
Yeah, that'd be crazy.
I'm not going to do anything.
I'm not going to do anything weird.
I'm just going to leave you.
It's for people.
This is only two more days.
Someone said that she pulled out the,
they pulled out the Karen phones.
I am.
I said, I said, that was the pier.
Are you sure?
I said, you're on YouTube.
We're cool.
Oh, I'm leaving right now.
I'm not going to try to come back in or anything.
I didn't do anything wrong.
See, then the other one came out.
The other turn came out. Look, they're going to come back on me. I'm not doing anything wrong.
Look at all the people there.
There's guarding the floor.
Look out for that integer
I was pulling out the Karen Brigitte on me, dude
Dave!
It's not a Karen
I didn't even fucking do anything wrong
Don't go to the bed store, please don't go to the mattress
Please don't, don't bother the lady in the mattress
Yeah, she's like searching me down there
Like trying to flag down security or something
This is nuts
I mean, I'm not gonna run
But I hate Disney
Alright, so let me sit down here
Is it okay if I take my shoes off and kind of oh, okay, cool. So you probably before I don't take them off
Sorry, I have a little autism in the way that I sleep is really weird. I usually start with something like this on my back
Playback Tommy James imagine all the police
Oh
She's gonna tell a customer how much would how much is this again
He's not gonna buy it lady if it does that hardness feeling time to go away it feels a little hard
I take it the more you sleep in it and break it in all beds kind of have that I'm not familiar with memory so much.
Well this one is broken in so this is how it would feel.
This is how it would feel because I can't help but think like oh my legs.
Call the police now.
I'm fine, I'm fine, this is normal.
Now, you're really listening to me.
I actually do that about every night before I fall asleep.
I have crazy night cares.
Kind of what I was looking for,
but the hope was some of this.
Watch, watch.
But honestly, even just putting me,
like sitting like this is putting me in a really dark place.
Well, let's get you off then.
Let's get you off the floor.
Out of this floor!
Out!
No, I'm getting up right now. Let's see. It's gonna take us
That oh my god moaning on your temper that was total work. Oh
I wonder what
I heard a whisper call the police call police
Did I do are you calling the police on me? No, not on you on the other I'll just leave
Are you calling the police on me?
Nobody's outside nobody's within five miles
Can you tell me what he looks like?
So I don't get attacked out there.
Sorry, that scared the hell out of me.
Because I see everybody looking outside
and I'm wondering what's going on.
That's pretty scary.
You guys deal with that a lot?
Oh, it happened.
Is he dangerous?
Not necessarily.
Just to have him annoying more than anything.
Yeah, they were definitely trying to call the police on me. I'm not fucking stupid
I'm not fucking stupid
I'm gonna be fuck out of here
Jesus Christ, I didn't even get to the other store yet you guys, and they're already pulling this shit on a nickel
They're about to get arrested
Oh, all right chat be ready for an interaction with the police apparently they're gonna find me
I'm right here
So they're gonna find me they're gonna fucking give me hell. I might get detained for nothing
Let's just go.
I think I freaked her out a little bit much
with the autism.
We're gonna get the fuck going.
Yeah, they're all like peeking out the windows looking at me.
I'm not fucking stupid.
She tells that guy,
oh, can you call the police discreetly?
Why the fuck would you need to call them discreetly?
And I say come on dog
Dude acting like I'm gonna fucking do something crazy. I'm not dangerous, dude
I'm getting the fuck out of there. We're switching locations
We'll finish our IRL over here on this part and if something happens something happens
Timmy's you're right
The callers are telling them crazy shit. I didn't think about that. Oh my god
Dear god somebody just needs to tackle this fucking guy
That's psyche when he turns into a Terminator
This one looks good easy this one looks good hold on one second when I see one more here look at this
Do you like this guy
It's me
The real reason you're stiff after sitting you can live a very long sitting
You fucking beat that, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah,
Be da just be da
That's what they're singing
That one's good when I he turned fully white. I like that one. Oh here. I'm here. I'm what am I saying?
I want to play. Oh, I don't know. I'll get it on
But now it's over
They please there's no link because I'm not on stream yard or or anything
But you can talk from the chat and black RG. So let me see. See you good guy
Not particularly the first time I came across black RG
He was doxing Vita did a whole it a whole episode and well now I don't even care that you did that
But it did lead into you know him telling that he had a spy
Okay, that's good. He had a spy in my discord all time, and you okay fine. You're not a good guy then
Yeah, he's just he wants to be everyone's friends, you know until he like fucking betrays them and steps on the back
There I was mad. Oh, I don't know. I like black really fair
Vita stuff sure
but uh
Black RG. I'm neutral on black RG. I'm neutral. Hey, my shirt's gonna come off. Yeah
So I would say the the word the most evil person. I would say it's Vita. She is the fakest person absolutely the fakest person
biggest
I don't know just fake she's just fake a new name fake friend buddy troll liar
She lets people be abused, let her friends be abused.
She also, she will not go live without like having
a bunch of people lined up to defend her.
This is true.
She'll even, and I know about this for a fact,
who she mails and says, oh come on in.
She might have been me.
Yeah, but you guys, the history is years long of it.
I know.
I knew it's funny about you that she said.
I just started streaming.
Oh, you did it really?
Oh, you just started, really?
You've been around for years and years and years.
She disappeared for a while for a reason. I'm sure she did
You can tell me that reason. I'm sure everyone like to hear
Because she's just the worst, you know, so fake
so fake
There's just a fake had a look in the dictionary under fake her pictures
Everything her and then she doesn't look anything like even even her bad pictures are flattering her. Okay, I'll put it that way
McDonald's coffee awful awful awful person. I
Agree, I like this guy the Alex is another one that came in
Super friendly super my friend and then it's like I said one thing she didn't like
The Eric dude is next who's Eric
Oh, yeah, Alex is talking to
Well, look at Tommy James look at poor Tommy James. He's today smoking in a smoking crack in the little room. I
mean
God
Poor Tommy James that isn't a curse. I don't know what is
You suck you fucking suck bitch
Hey, dude, let me just play like an hour and a half of like donating music so I make some money
Yes, boys and she's a 9,000 year old vampire, man, right, right
Oh, no Alex not I'm not doing that fucking suck you suck
You sit there two hours 85 messages. I already got it in five minutes. Okay. Go fuck yourself bitches
GO FUCK YOURSELVES
YOU SUCK
86 87 keep keep commenting chat comment super chat come on guys guys
Let's make this a big one because a big night. Okay. Let's like dethrone those bitches
I'm sick of salmon and betas keep green of the streamer birds. They fucking suck
They suck they suck my buttle go away
No one wants to listen to you anymore. I am the shit now. I'm the new shit. You suck
Let's get to 100. I like this guy. I see a hundred messages. Just comment a BCD
I don't care. I want to say a hundred messages right now. I'm leaving
I can crash that over. Oh, there we go. A hundred! A hundred!
Fuck you bitches!
Fuck you bitches! I'm more popular than you already!
I've been on the street for a year. You've been up for years! Years!
You want what I have. You want what I have, bitches.
You will never get it because you're not me. You're not me, okay?
I'm the best.
You'll never find better than,
you'll never find better than me.
102 messages, hey, fuck, yes.
Sam, man, you're a bitch.
Sam, man, you're a fucking bitch.
That's all I need to say.
I agree.
I need to give you any elaboration on it.
You're just a bitch.
Go fucking bend over for your Riker's Island boyfriend.
I know you had one.
Sam, man, got fucked in the ass.
More than I have and I'm gay. Okay, I'm gay. He's been fucked up. He asked more than I have. Okay
Beedah likes that too. She likes to be fucked in the ass.
Beedah, I know you do.
This anal queen, 1999, whatever fucking year it was,
graduated high school, I have to fuck up the ass
by half the football team.
I know of all about you.
Oh, boy.
Beedah, all about you.
I hear all about her.
He knows I'm going too far.
Beedah, Miss Eye Tags, 1999.
I know all about it, bitch!
Die!
This is what it's about. It's about real. It's about being real. It's not a fake bitch like you are.
You're just a big bitch. You're still a sad man. Go fuck yourself.
I'm a real one. I'm a real one in the chat. Anyone who's ever talked to me offline or offline, online or offline, knows.
I'm a fucking real one. It's not a fake bitch like you are.
Or Mr. Sandman, just fake, only gonna drop a link for me.
Fake, fake, fake, die, fucking die, bitch.
You wanna have some real shit tonight?
You wanna have a real fun stream?
That was a cool-
That was a super shout.
I am the fool, Alexandra, I am the fool, Alexandra.
You can't let them get under your skin, bro. You can't let them do that.
I am a fool, Alexandra. I am.
I was never believing you!
I was entertaining the chat.
To believe in you! To love you!
I'm an idiot!
I'm not okay, ghost. I'm not okay.
I'm not okay.
I'm done with it.
These liars, these fake fraudulent human beings
even call them bad, it's disgusting.
They suck, they suck.
I'm done.
I'm gonna go jump off a cliff.
I'm done with it.
Fucking Sam and
No, I didn't hear it. I didn't hear it. I don't care you suck. You suck
Why am I less popular than you? I don't know because people are dumb
Erick and Mike. I know we're the stroke off twins. I want to do a jerk off shoot with that
I don't remember this. No, I don't stroke off. Can you come over here, please?
All I do is try to help you Alexander too. All I do is how to help you. Try to tell you where Eldo is. Oh, I blocked
Bitch, you just asked for where he is. I told you. Are you dumb? Are you dumb?
You're dumb. I try to tell you you blocked me. You are dumb
Really, I don't want to say the stupid community is dumb, but go to Sam and
Oh, you're so funny. Oh
No, I don't hear you. I don't fucking know you I didn't hear I didn't hear those dumb I can't take it
That's what I heard I had WR there's a retard
Go to hell bitch
That's what I heard
Watch paint dry, you know on a reverse a hundred times. They fucking suck
They're the worst
the worst
I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so sorry, I'm so
I mean, Jesus Christ, you suck ass!
Alexander Mayer's, a thousand times better
than you on your best day.
On her worst day, Alexander Mayer's,
is a thousand times better than you.
She doesn't even like me.
She's better than you.
You suck.
You're the worst.
The fucking worst.
Go to fucking hell, you bitches.
You suck.
You suck nobody wants to see on stream yard. They're gonna realize that I'm better
They're gonna come to me and be like why wasn't even a beat-in Samans in my life. They fucking suck
I must have been you know have brain dead even play with them. I
Know I wasn't a 1.2
Okay, well that was yeah, I like that guy right there. I don't know who that was but yeah
He's a good guy that guy was a fucking amazing
It was amazing. Yeah, he was you fucking let that shit out
Hey, you know, it's like that's that's called real. Let's call real just like you know what you know, she said it tonight. She's like, oh
oh, um, uh
I'm gonna quit streaming because I have a guilty conscience because I was made you know, psyche and alive himself
You know, that's what I mean. It's like really that's what's funny to you making s-u-i-c. I need jokes
Really, okay
Sike at the end of the day, bro. You don't let these motherfuckers get under your skin, bro
Let him use fucking laugh at them. That's no dumb
I'm done. I'm done. I'm done with that. Oh my god. Oh, that's been a picture of him two months apart
He looks like he's he's dying because I'm eating an apple or a burger with a oh
I'm like, I have like the word, especially like,
like, I mean, oh, people were in the chatter,
like, oh, are his teeth falling out?
Like, in this picture, like, what's going on?
Why does he have an Adam's apple?
Why is his neck like that?
Look at him eating something!
You're so stupid!
I'm done with it!
Okay, I'm sorry.
Yeah, slow down, slow down, psyche.
Take a deep breath.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
You're just gonna be so mad.
Oh, Peter, oh, Peter's gonna stew me, so is Alex!
I'll see you in court!
I'll see you in fucking court!
I'm gonna win on Riverside myself higher Robert Shapiro. I'm gonna win. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa down Ronys down
Do that's what I'm saying, baby. Thank you peel exactly, but no corruption. You passed the test. I
Left you up here along with Ronys my Ronys by the way. I don't leave Ronys along with just anyone. I
Left you up here with Ronys
And you passed the test you actually handled them well you calmed them down you had his back
Good job
You guys call it crazy or him crashing I call it healthy release of energy
If he didn't know that fucking
That you will make him sick bro if he held all that shit in oh, yeah
Just taking my like this extra energy of mine, and it's like I'm about to explode
Let them take that's your point. That's the point if you let them take it TV TV
I'm still in a phone with TV TV. I hope it's not a fucking 500 pound fat kind
I don't hope because I don't know who the fuck it is
You listen bitch
I'm crazy like psyche. We fight with the we fight with the
I
Michael Michael was everyone's in your penis except for me
No one's seen my pianist
Like girls from like years ago, like this is a Michael league was linguine we call them linguine
But it was a Michael league was almost something he died
He was a friend of ours up here and he passed away recently
Really can't like I wish I wish
Falling we I miss me something we these who's the nicest guy up here by the way
I don't care if he was gay or not he was still nice and guy up here, bro
Be the love
Okay, it would be this for it says QQ. He's a bird. He said it's better than I thought you were talking to me
Thank you, then you tell Q to hit the link they'll listen to you then I don't listen to Alex
If you say Q
I miss you when I talk to you. No, he might get the link because of monsters
Big tall just takes over all things over all this keeps taking over the big tall
How about you fucking suck the juice out of your fucking fucking ex-girlfriend's ass, called Tracy
He loved it, they loved it, he was too cool for school, bro
Girls like just cool dudes, like none of the pecs, like right there, he's playing beat-a, like a pick-a-notha
Last one she's like, wow, I love this guy, like he doesn't suck my day
You will literally eat her
When you're the one that even making fucking correct pronouns
Everybody put one in the
choose your own
all angry panels tonight.
So people get to know him because
corruption doesn't even know who we're talking about.
I know
I
Remember the greenie with his dog and his girl
The juice that comes out
Yo, you gotta play the song too Psyche. Oh, welcome to the madness Michael taking flight Alex something
Welcome to the
No
Just admit it psyche it may you missed be the more than anything forget mayors
You like mayors. You're a nice guy. You miss fucking beta
Hey
Girl is dying without you, bro
I told you dick
You know they're gonna love you psyche bro man you're she would be to forget everything else
She's glazing I feel like I'm talking to them on the panel from 10 years ago which is weird
let me give him whatever he wants we're gonna hold it right here if we see it
like somebody looking like um michael
Thank you
Thank you, then we record me a whore last night
Me and bronze
Why don't you by the way psyche we go further than we thought I saw a video last night from a year ago
With all of us on it. I just blindfolded
not 11 months and then say oh, it's Vita here
And you have just had talking to the ear like oh, it's Vita Vita, and then
Right
Is a seagull he's a bird
You know the Chris Isaac video, you know that one song yeah, what's that song?
Oh, that's crazy because beat it was on fucking Brownsburg the other day
in each other's eyes and that bronze bird is going to
Yeah just like you keep that eye on the chat my man I'm not down there what
past because I'm up here with you guys nobody's got to watch that hit
before they sneak some dumb shit in there yes plays in that's why yes so I have a
song I'm going to sing okay it goes I need to hear the lyrics though
The world was on fire and no one could save me but you. It's strange what desire will make those people do
I never dreamed that I'd meet somebody like you
Dream that I'd lose somebody like you
Don't wanna fall in love
He knows the worst every song on the planet, by the way, by the way.
With a wicked game to play to make me feel this way.
What a wicked, this way, dick, dick, dick, dick, let me sleep, fuck you.
And I never dreamed I'd find somebody like you
And I never dreamed that I'd do somebody like you
And I wanna fall in love with you
When you really love this fucking dog, huh?
I'll be with you
Yeah
Okay, I like that video
And then they tell our psyche you were in front of the guy
This guy spent they spent every day together
I don't know how long we knew whether he was gonna go or not, but this guy was always giving us the best advice and trying to look out for me.
Blogger was like, oh, because I was mentioning, I said clumsy and he's like, oh, but isn't there like a different clumsy?
Blogger's been watching my show, he knows who clumsy Clairvoyance is. I mean, he's into my, he's into my, what's it called, into my lore.
He knows my lore of my show already.
Yeah, I can just get him.
You want me to contact him?
I can get him.
Yeah, go get him.
Can you come on here, Ho?
Yeah.
Get your butt up, Ho.
Come on up here, blogger.
Blogger you, Ho.
Only problem is that he will actually form a meal,
not on purpose.
It's OK.
If I see something that may get a thrill,
I can always end the stream.
I'll give you an example.
He has way too many heart.
Lebanese, what do you call that?
Hard Mike?
Until Lebanese.
So he got naked, and we're like, okay, everybody, like, okay, it's a little naked mess.
And then he put a fucking paper plate on his playlist area.
I don't know if that's okay, his censor, and then he got up, he, like, he was, he was
rapping, and we were having fun, all that shit, and he forgot he had the paper plate on his
He went to go to the bathroom for a second, and we saw all the balls, but out of the plate,
you know, the dick was showered, it was incredible.
Oh my god blogger
We can look at you guys like I said, I was like this one guy. I forgot his name
He like how to crush on me
I think he was like the name is saw sawed or sawed or something like that and he's like
Like can I come on panel and I was and he's like and I was like, okay. Well, just
You can be in boxers and stuff and he was in his boxers
But he was completely aroused in the boxers and then he showed his feet the bottom of his feet
And they were like green and I was like, oh my god
Can't let him on the panel anymore
And no, well your band
I know he was big tall as already big tall knows Alisa, you know
I know I know you are
What's your problem?
William is having a poll whether he died I think tall you have like a little tiny little worm
Shut up, bitch question
I'm turning to psyche. I'm starting to fight with video from a year ago. It's like he does it
I thought psyche the other day yelling at me on a video. I wasn't there. It was an old video
He was like shut up
He but I'm gonna ask you a question William to fire home. He better have fucking died
He better have because that's one of the thickest jokes if he didn't okay
If he didn't die I'm gonna find everybody who was involved in that joke
Are you going to give her the trophy?
Yeah, the trophy.
Check it out.
Beat it.
You're...
Okay, the thing is, between me and you,
Of course he died, who would lie about dying, Esso?
Just like the other people that will probably
potentially come on this live panel.
They're gonna all try and get on my skin.
Listen to him, listen to him,
because he, no, Linguini was too cool for school.
Listen to him.
He gave that large human right away like this.
Can I negate that?
He joined the panel.
Yeah
Like
I didn't mean Michael. I don't know who that is a little ripped to him. Oh, so who the fuck are you talking about William?
All right, William, let me fill you in corruption. Are you listening?
Alright, so see the guy in the middle Michael league was on man, whatever
Right. He was on this panel from like day one with psyche very good friend
We were all up here. We all know him stomach like all you all are all your family
We all know
That's Michael almost started. They said he died
The guy died
for his funeral and now people that have a conspiracy like they really died or did they make that shit up?
and that's where we're at my man
America America America what do you think bro you think so we'll lie about that
You should go back to your room
No, no, no, I didn't mean it that way
Nah, bro
His mom
No, his mom confirmed that they called his mom, bro
You know how people call people's jobs to get them fired?
They called his mom to confirm it
Am I talking over Bita on a panel from 10 years ago?
Like, this is crazy
This is crazy, so when this dumb bitch shuts up on this panel and then we talk her up again.
Because I'm fighting a panel from ten years ago right now.
I'm losing my mind.
Oh my god, I didn't even mean it that way.
What do you want?
I didn't mean it that way, I'm sorry.
Like legit, if it came off that way, legit.
I'm sorry.
you're getting hot it's getting hot in here because i told you i'll cook you when it gets to the
fucking hot in the kitchen i didn't mean it that way dita i was born in this country
okay what the fuck are you talking about i read in this class my dad got this fucking pc here we go
You want me to tell you my degree? What do you have? What's your age? You don't need to. Why not? At your age, I would already be doing way more than that.
Did I ask you for your degree? Did I ask you for your degree?
No, you can't waste that from me and you said that.
Okay, so you wanted to show me.
Listen, I didn't mean it that way. I did not mean it that way.
Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael, Michael.
You speak a different language?
You dumbass bitch?
I didn't mean it that way. Okay.
I was trying to talk about my fucking I was born in this
country before I didn't know you were from the Middle East.
You know that before you look at the screen.
I didn't know that you were from the Middle East.
I didn't know that even from the Middle East Asia.
I even said India.
They're fucking South Korea like what the fuck like listen
All I was trying to say was that who ever talks to me
Anyway, I don't know why I argue with this fucking bitch as whole
when people don't fucking defend me
when I defend them for hours
I can go two hours defending fucking bitches and fucking dickheads
but I gotta argue with this bitch
and some people will be sitting in the trash
I think it was a bath, alright
I think he's gonna turn and giggle
Are you gonna die?
I'm not a fucker, say I'm an auto-minor-consider that I'm a shorn-eer.
My business know you're a little bitch.
You're sorry. I'm sorry. Sorry. I'm sorry
When they go call me ugly when people shit on me nobody joins that link to fight for me, but I'll do that I
Would I would I would
Bitch, oh my god, D. Just a lot it, huh?
Yeah
I was fighting a panel. I'm about to jump in again. Like shut up bitch
The fuck up Peter. I'm about to jump in again, my man
She probably killed him this guy probably jumped up a bridge after hanging out this big think about it like yo
Peter's out there. I'm out bridge
Now, listen to me, imagine coming home to Vita, thank you, did you make money today, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you,
Wow, and then he died and then he died. That should be
Then the next week the guy dies after this
Me and or message me and take it as soon as I see it. I'll be there. Okay
You know, I will. Okay. I love you. I'll always defend you. Okay.
I just gotta say, I will fucking go to pot with so many fucking people.
But when he goes to me, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet.
He goes away. She's here crying you come the tears. Hi. Oh, no
Tracy the wait the witch number two is crying shut the fuck up. Yeah, so now we got beat up crying and
Attacking my cold it was Tombo and look at him. He's laughing at these bitches
Fucking racist
He told me that I should know what's what I mean because that's a black
time. He told me, you know, you got me beefing with
battles from ten years ago. I love you after that.
He's a fucking racist and you don't fucking hurt Bita like that.
But you know, if you turn around and you still are,
I know I'm being a panel that can't be a fucking girl with you.
I don't know. You understand what's going on, mental.
this is not normal
And this was Psyche's friend, by the way, he hits that dog, I fucking seen that shit.
And this is real fucking shit.
He's a motherfucking lot.
Look at me, girl, open it.
No, I don't.
Listen, Psyche, just look at me, girl.
Look at me.
I'm gonna be quiet. It's fine
You ain't never talking about a bitch ass thing. You are mark-ass motherfuckin look at the wheel
You fucking made my girl
The motherfucking earth you made my girl
At the same time, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be quiet, I'll be
Sorry ass mother fucker sitting in your mama house that you lied and said that you own
I own two cars. I own this house. I own everything you own nothing, but I lie you are lie. You are true fucking fake
You done faked everybody on this goddamn panel everybody in a motherfucking chat
fucking pussy
You don't even deserve pussy
I don't know what Academy of whooping ass he went to but you know, it's crazy
I think we were in the same class. I remember lingering early. Who's having like I knew we were in the same class
And this dude got affected by what we expected going to town in these pages. He doesn't understand that
You know I'm saying
This is this is cock suckers. That's not Ron's bird is such a cock sucker. It's scary, bro
This guy will suck anybody's dick. I gotta hold it down for the girls because I gotta teach this man
What a real man is you understand especially psych you understand that
No, go ahead. Go ahead and do your thing because you know, I think
You don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil, you don't have no oil
At the end of the day that these two women are strong enough to go against bastards like Michael
Right what's up?
What's going on bronze so what you good? I'm good. That's what's up increase your beta if ever like
Good to see you
Take care of it like you want to take care of it because I think you're great. It's just taking over yourself
I know you're talking you're a strong
So
Yeah, I'm good and I appreciate all the laughing things we need everything I came up here for be better
He's disrespectful and he's a liar
at this. This is just like a show for him. You know, all the same. It's on here. All day. All night.
Live.
The same shit. You don't let me tell my story. I'm fighting with a panel from 90 years ago.
He always looks at this off narrative that he's crazy. I'm just fucking sick of it.
He can be where he wants to be. No one's trying to control that, but fucking be real for fucking once.
It's pathetic to keep sitting there, never ever ever holding his own shit and owning the shit that he does.
I can't stand a motherfucker like that. We all fuck up in life. He never owns his shit.
Mm-hmm
He just sits on the panel and just takes up fucking space for someone else to be there who really gives a shit.
I just want peace. I don't want peace.
You don't want peace, bro. You don't want peace, bro. I'm lying.
You just told me fuck you and I called me a bitch.
If I were a rich fucking female like that, you would have a problem with that.
Don't fucking disrespect me.
When did I call you
The tracy do like a demon exchange of spirits
I'm out of here, but you girls take over my demon spirit
It's a job
every time i shed a tear you're gonna pay out of it because you i think the greenies protects you
psyche right his spirit he loved you and he was a queen he's still working protecting your funky
your motherfucking hands around your motherfucking throat.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
you heard what she said?
That's because you wear a buckle
and you want to fuck your throat,
and you got it, that's the thing.
I'll choke the shit out of you, bitch.
You better watch your motherfucking mouth.
You really never knew me, ho.
No, you wouldn't.
You really never knew me.
Your hands are too tight to do that, you can't.
Shut the fuck up.
Wow, did she just say, I'll choke the shit out of you bitch, you better watch your fucking mouth like an evil bitch.
She did, right?
Yeah, and look at Linguini, Linguini laughing at all.
Do you see how special Linguini was, brother?
I'm not even talking to you, I'm on you, I'm not even talking to you, I'm on you, I'm not even talking to you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you, I'm on you
Oh, now you want to switch it over to you?
Don't talk about his mother either, hoe.
Shut your head, bro.
Don't talk about his mother either.
You don't want nobody mentioning your goddamn mama
that you don't even respect.
You even have to talk down on your mama?
I'd have heard you tell your mama to get the fuck out
of bed.
I'd have heard you tell your mama to get her ass out of bed,
just like that.
I'd have heard you talk to your mama like that.
Bitch, bro.
Tell your mama to get up.
I'd have heard you talk to her like that.
Oh, damn, you're fucking hoodie in your hat, motherfucker.
I bet you was not even fucking hot in your house or cooling your house. We're a fucking hood in the hat
goofy
Go ahead unmute. I want you to say something bitch. It's made ass. Yeah, I'm wasting my motherfuckers
Nurse and me the nurse and me made me think I
Motherfucking ass back to some sensibility. You will waste a motherfucking life
Fucking I will never fucking like you. I'll just tell you how much
Gave c-section to a fag
We love psyche
That's crazy. It's just crazy how
These two I don't have a recorder
I'm sure I have some more intention
because I got too long internet
y'all just make me pay less
Michael you don't even have a fan on me
but what how you making money
you ain't making the money up to cheap
what's your famous score dude
what's your famous score
look at all those evils around psyche right now
and we need
just smiling
with this cute little thing we need to pay
right?
no evil, no bad words
no negative energy
he was just a special dude
We do shit.
Yeah, you're a girl who pays for it.
Howdy kids, I'm not sure I asked you, do you know what I'm saying?
I just haven't to keep dealing with this stuff.
You watching?
Weenies, weenies, weenies, weenies, weenies, weenies, weenies,
Oh, and I mean that, me and Jamie Cowboys alone.
Stand her fucking discord.
You don't think you about shit, bitch.
It was it was two messages and it was like me Jamie taboids alone. Like I said, leave alone leave all these women alone
Oh, so you so you still from women as that's what you saying that's his thing
Or you just admitted that but he told pa he was gonna give him $30. I guess that was gonna come from me
Oh, yeah. So that's what you want.
I hope those things are broke.
But don't let me address me, bitch.
You ain't good enough to say my mother's fucking name ever again in this motherfucking life.
Don't say my goddamn name, bitch.
Unless you don't allow for parking like a motherfucking dog.
Oh, you would give me money again.
So you bitch, you know, money for 20 come out of his face for summer.
And that was like, wow, he never does.
Oh, that's all you can ever do for me.
That'll never happen with Guini.
If you ever so greedy come out of space that means Jesus is coming down from heaven or there's an atomic bomb on the way
I don't know Tracy that well, and I don't fucking know shit. I know enough that I know you're a scumbag
Hey, you got the you got the balls to go in her pan
Exactly
Just to you got the nerve to go up panel, you know why
You know why? I'll tell you why.
It's a fucking sad life.
When somebody like Tracy is an angel
and she's got to fucking do what she's got to do to make money,
and you fucking hustle that shit,
and you think, oh boy, spend my more nights with friends.
That's cute, huh?
It's gonna be good when you start crying, though.
It's gonna be real good.
Yeah, you're gonna cry, bitch.
You got your day coming
With a real man is you understand
Hey, hey, look, take this out. Maybe I could take your girl
Let me tell you that maybe I could take your girl too, Michael. How about that?
Can I see some kids now?
Can I just talk for a minute?
Can I talk for a minute?
They're Tracy right now said
I got a thing with fucking Brownberg
I would be like damn
Brownberg's the biggest shit
You're a bitch out of fucking home Michael
But you're not a man
This guy up here fucking fighting for her
And not even he doesn't even know her
He didn't need to ask her for money
Or you don't know
Fuck you man
You're a pussy fucking Michael
You're gonna sit there and think this is shit. It's funny. You just
I think that's enough of this but you know, I just want to show you
that I do have this, this is my new website called Codex.
And that's what this is all from.
It's like all organized.
I organize every single guest, every single topic.
I like, you know, easy's in there.
Every single person's on the show.
Every single person's on the chat is in there.
All the episodes are gonna be cataloged.
That's why I found this one tonight.
and I'll show you real quick this is like uh what do you mean every episode that you've ever
had is over 1000 of them they're all transcribed they're all summarized and every guest is put
into their own um like wikipedia kind of thing and you can type in like alex or easy and it'll
that's crazy
that's insane
that's technology now
that's so cool
guys
yeah, now we're fucked easy, right?
you know what that means
so let's go up there baby
242 people
393 lower entries
this is as much as a bar
388 quotes
Every episode is gonna be in here everything the every person on this show
And her people
It's gonna bring you to every Alexander McQueen episode that I've been on on your panel since I met you
That is crazy if that's true
And very cool
Yeah
Alexander Alex loud computational panel regular
Berries there guess who accuses beta blocking him on our channel and engages in heated arguments
I think there are what episodes are on then you can click on the episode and we'll take you to whatever episodes are on
You know, that's insane. How'd you do that, bro?
That's crazy for months. We're here for months, you know, basically or that is just like a TVP or library
That you can click on like episode to call the psyches library, but for him
It's free cult codex dot me and you can I'll go to it
Your website or it's like a line someone else's and
Made it. Wow every single episode
you can see my cat magic in all these episodes. All right, all right, it's called
all right. So that's a good episode that like a memorable episode. We can go to
episodes. That was one good one. I'm making but I don't I only have already diamond episodes
were always great. Those were always amazing. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I will say these are my beginning ones I've only like 50 or 60 I can only do like a certain amount of day
And I just got got these up today. There's children was on there. Very cool man. Very cool
I'm a Leviathan. Hey, um, let me see. So he's like a little week
30 diamond was there it says 30 diamond young person who has conflicts with their panel guests and left upset after heated exchanges
You know, I promised a party. This is the first appearance. Let me see
I don't let me see if I can find her. Oh, no pull up a page of some are going crazy. Oh against anybody
I said something to you. No put summer put summer. How many
Here from her they someone talk to you right there's people that are there trying to ruin relationship like wow
Okay, so I'm saying you have to I was on this panel
Yeah
Nothing better and people will probably say actually watch the other night everyone about me and something that and they'll say
Oh sake he's saying this about you, and I would never talk about that little dog thing is sweepy by the way
Break up over. Oh, this person said this they're saying this and they won't even I'll say what did I do wrong?
We're like, oh, you know what you did like I'm like, what did I do? They're like, oh, you know
Then there'll be no resolution
People will try to ruin relationships that are close. Okay, so you have these relationships
You don't have to listen to other people other people getting your ear. It's like a totally earworm
And this is a year ago. He's saying this guys
You gotta tell
People is today like the money for 20
Thank you for saying this a year
Like what what you think it's true, you know, it's like a page
But don't let it get to you when you know what's true and what's not inside of you
This week before she was the dolphin. She didn't know she was gonna be a dolphin
It's very virtual when I know that she's doing this on other panels, you know, oh my god
I hear all the time people said about you on the panel. I never ever like go and check it out. I'm just like
They can say to my face if they really believe that
Ever
i will come up here and i'll come front you and you'll be silent as soon as i leave you're gonna
fucking sit there and lie thank you how did you provide the cycle what do you want me to tell
you how strong you are you were surrounded by like i'm not gonna let you the only few people that
Stop lying. Oh my gosh, are you really serious?
Damn bro, it's like any family to go to in the future.
I think there's some kind of battle, like the purple heart of something.
This guy went to the war with these fucking hokers.
Yeah, who's saying that's the Crystal Marie?
Who said who?
50 on three years.
Peter said this, Peter said that.
I don't think you've heard on a page.
Nobody, it's our fucking delusion.
All I ever do is like, oh my God, I love Crystal Marie.
I'm gonna show all your messages, right?
And then...
Oh my god, he's the only guy up there
I think
Fucking beef. They're almost out of them. I don't know respect. Let's see Alexander thing
Let me see I'll go episode I'll go people and I go Alexander and then I will say see Alexander and I come that Alex
And I will say damn a boring one. Give me uh, you're here. Look at this one. Give me a piranha
Thank you, I don't want to hear my soul a year ago
Is that her is it her Michael or is that a different one she doesn't want to vouch for you Michael
That's kind of dry that's kind of dry bro. Oh, yeah, did you breathe?
Are you high-fiving?
You hoping that you get your turn
Canada
Yep
Oh
I don't want to hear what I said
Sorry, I was digging a lot
You have me like you know, you know, you always want me to get manicure and sublative that
I'm like
She was gonna read you so my rainy and shit and I was like I don't hear it
No, well, I know what it's gonna be. Yeah, so I
Love Alex and the story. I don't need your reading. You're winning. Get up
Persian reading
Sikes, okay. Yeah, exactly. Take a read. Can we have the last night beta?
You gotta focus you're being disrespectful
Yeah, but yeah, these are really cool, Alex.
Just say stop.
Yeah, say stop, Alex, when everyone is stop.
Stop I'm just kidding. I'm not being this stuff. Oh, and I'm completely joke
Do not mess with this guy right here
That's how it is. I'm trying to concentrate. Okay. Alex. Is that you give me a fucking
But I think you're fucking with me that's why I don't believe you. I'm trying to concentrate
This is special style reading only person people can do will do this kind of reading
Which
I'm gonna ask
Are you ready guys check this out?
Were you just speaking in tongue? What was that?
He's going to try to blow the spell on me to marry her sastre. Let her continue with them spells
You know
You ruined it. Alex. Alex you're supposed to say
He doesn't want he doesn't need it
I'm going to give you a reading I was asking how
many I had with a glass of wine like like whatever please
answer Alejandro's questions.
How can I know?
Nice to meet you.
Bro, what a fucking hell, Sask.
Sask.
This is how.
Just follow my lead pal.
I know that you didn't just say this.
You want to leave.
Live.
Live with me, bro.
Okay, bro.
Sask, you want to fucking watch it.
Do not go with this guy.
I'm behind now.
There's the bitch in the middle.
I like stick to it.
You got your family.
You understand?
You didn't know that, did you?
You didn't know being a stature family.
You told me just mad.
I
It's it's doing something nice and you were like being so disrespectful
Okay, no, no, I love you psyche
Yes, he said yes do it and then when I try to do it he said no
But then what stacks just did what said you have Alexander's back
Are you gonna do that because if you want to vouch for that you're on a fucking ride?
you're on a big ride right now sax you want to vouch for alexander listen you know i thought it was
a joke because you i couldn't understand it it was a language you give me a reading in the
language i don't understand you know i was asking him i was telling him i was telling him i was
Don't give me a ring in Iranian Iranian. I don't understand that bullshit. Oh my god
This is before I knew the war was gonna happen by the way
It might defend
That was a going out of you a stupid asshole you're reading
and so a thousand times i said alexander tell me when to stop i keep trying to do it in my head
i keep asking him like uh you know i didn't hear the poet for a fucking answer but he kept
interrupting me so i said it out loud i said a hard job for this you know i got you because
No, I I hear you. I didn't hear that maybe he didn't either. We thought you just started speaking and
You guys are like talking and like in the yelling and stuff like that and it's like
Alex is the one speaking in tongues
It's very it's very frustrating like when I do readings too
It's someone saying like the other night I was on good times
I'm like, they're good good times are reading and I was like trying to give good times reading. It's like, oh, no
You're not doing it right. You're just throwing up the energy and it's like, oh, I got it back.
Okay. So let's all come down. KK, are you here? I'm here. Hi. Good evening. Hi. Good evening.
Hi, girl. Yeah, that was very, very
I just asked the poet guy, like, can you answer this retard's question called Alexander?
I don't get why people think it's so weird when we speak our native language.
What's the issue?
You guys are so uncultured, idiots, uncultured, you know what I'm saying?
Nobody cares. Congratulations. You're leading your life.
Who does not understand the language?
I'm just saying...
He's a European and she's like,
he knows how to speak a different language.
Look at it. He's trying to front his weed now.
Wow. Wow.
He's starting to smudge between his fingers.
It's really impressive.
No, that's a joke.
You gotta take that act on the road, bro.
I've never seen that before.
You're disrespectful and it's like yeah, there's different languages. I love I love Sam's great and Indian
and I love I love listening to the Arabic prayers too or the
And she said, can I give you a reading?
I said yes, and then she talks to me.
She's letting me back up, right?
Fucking misunderstanding, guys.
Just like TVP.
She's just keep letting me back up.
She's not going to be touching her language.
She's like, what is this?
It's a baby.
This guy was just on the panel like a few days ago like white nighting like you needed protection and he was going to protect you and now he's up here
angry seems like he's got like angry man syndrome or something
He went and turned and I don't know what his deal is
Can you give me my reading bitch in English that's all I want
Don't ever say
You know you're being way out of here, okay Alex
What she does
She was doing
I know that she left come back. I'm sorry. Okay. I'm sorry. I'm back. I'm sorry. I'll take him up. Okay. I
Don't think he understood it and now he's going. I know and it's like it was like it's like it was very disrespectful
Alex and it's like, you know, I asked you're a good person. Okay. Yeah, come back. I don't like I like she was doing something
With from her culture and that they and it's a special thing that they only usually will do with people
Oh, I completely get it. I've explained it, but I'm not gonna lie at the time
I had not heard so I was like, you know, how are we gonna understand this tarot reading?
Yeah, I'm not crashing out about it. But like yeah, no
I was slightly confused and it has nothing to do with being uncultured.
I just can't understand other languages culture.
But it's like, but like this is not aware that she was speaking another language.
There's my queen.
Yeah, it seems to be.
And also, because Hector sent in for a career reading.
So Hector, you want to just tell me that you're in chat right now.
It says.
You're your worst enemy you are your worst enemy Alexander
That's what it's doing. It says use all of you know your brain power. I don't it's not really saying brain cells
I don't want to be disrespectful, you know
Whatever you can gather and do not be upset because better things can come come upon you in life
Do not, um, let your stress and do not get mad at him.
Like he got right there in the sun.
That shit don't look right.
I don't know if he was smoking crack but he was smoking cigarette.
You have to do it your way.
It's better in the big bar.
And no matter what, it looks like you're smoking weed.
You're going to have some good news very soon.
You've been
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay, okay
The morning Michael poison. I don't even think like he has fully mourned them actually and he doesn't even know it
Honestly, you know the theory. I'm a psychologist. Stop
You're a Mormon
Nobody's fault
You know what they really would want is where I want to be happy and
PbG b Jamie Cowboys came back
Jamie's Cowboys in the blue face.
What's your apology for?
Besides psych, in me, I already apologize.
I think psych he has to, right?
Something's going on with the cowboys.
It's just, okay.
That has to be done.
Forget it, forget it.
It's just don't listen to other people.
TV, TV, dog.
No, I mean, I wish to not be hopeless.
Because when you hear it,
they're going to see it,
they're going to see it.
It's just people that ask you for advice,
or give you advice,
you actually know better than them.
You know, the advice better than them. Okay. Um,
This is you're very smart and good
And um, I should be sorry you you're very smart and good and you know, how
You know
Okay
He's giving you the brains and like
Everything that you need to get to where you need to go where you paid you only got the little side plate
That's a
Bush back then
Maybe and love it out so big so I got one from Bay and thank you also for
For the donation and so it's careery for Bay, okay, so
So Bay
Yes, I don't know. Okay. Maybe it's something to do with criminal justice or something like that
57 watch like you believe this
Well three watching
Three watching
But everyone everyone needs
Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Okay.
Listen, guys, we forgive. We
forgive and forget. But don't
ever leave Psyche alone again.
You understand? And you're going
to become the master.
Until you get back on the high
water guy. You don't just
ditch the man. Okay. Yeah. If
you don't call a guy, you
just because somebody else
Same thing with last row to watching
It's like I would say God
Like you're put here to do something that will help
30 40 watching
90 watching
Something that's gonna bring you a lot of happy
They said I only had three people too, but
They should jump to
Arthur your boyfriend here. Okay
Oh, my man, R2J? R2J?
This is like releasing burdens from people also it can be
Yeah
Corruption have a great day be careful
Stay safe. Yeah, you gotta wake up early tomorrow, you say, and make the yeah everything was
Think what was it? There's like some there's like some
Some animated or like a cartoon strip where it's like the guys from Belgium and that was very popular
I can't remember exactly is the guy's little beady eyes are like little and he has a dog or something like that
I don't remember exactly. I'm kind of a lot of loss for it. There's like some some kind of like children's book or something
That was kind of popular
Belgium beady eyes and a dog
And guys, I want to thank you so much, guys.
Also, like a lot of people sent for a paid reading tonight.
I just want to thank you guys so much.
That mean that my cats and I really appreciate that, okay?
And we love you.
And I hope you can do your readings for everybody here.
And I'll still do readings tonight.
I still have a lot of energy tonight.
I took a little nap today that yeah,
we have a great panel going on.
Look at Sass, look at this cute guy right here.
Well, you're so cute.
Mary, is there sas?
OK.
I see you.
I didn't.
You need a reading?
I see you need a sas.
Yeah, I like a reader.
I heard you say something about reading on that panel.
I want to read it now.
Because I didn't get my monthly reading yet.
OK.
Oh
It's a prize reading the prize reading I love it
Remember when I need that can be weak right the monster
I was getting a deck in you
Oh
Okay, nine of wands this is like going towards something with a lot of energy like you're like a lot of excitement about something
You're like going towards it, but it's like just don't let it just don't like let it burn out like
Okay, you have the seven of wands to so this is like you're really really
on guard about something it's like you're not traumatized about it but you're
protecting something like definitely protecting something I see like a lot of fire energy around
right yeah okay always protecting my family I pre-sist this is like this is like some kind of like
either like a woman you're really close to or it's like it's like yourself is like uh has a
really high intuition about what's going on right now about this but the particular one is like this
Version Mary the version Mary. I don't know something about Catholicism Catholicism
Oh
And the Emperor okay the Emperor too this could be like I don't know if you're
This seems like like really coming into like some strength in this relationship
I think maybe are you with this really intuitive woman and you're like you're like you're coming to this power too
And you really really protecting everything. Let me just nobody would know. Well, would I get the heifer the heifers?
He's it's a he's into
That was a joke four cups is like really emotional and I'm really good emotional balance level
and i think whatever this relationship is it's like just really well balanced it's like i think it's
sound good to me it's a perfectly balanced oh judgment okay so judgment's being called in the
situation i like if something's been unfair and this one this one's a really nice one she's like
blowing like a little a little flute instead of like a like maybe it's true i think she's blowing
Page of cups. Okay. It's like it's gonna start something that's gonna kind of grow into something that will make you really happy
something that you're gonna be
Really emotionally invested in but but this is like a giant cock on behind. It's gonna be happy depends
You got this power you got the page of cups
it's
so easy what you get from that
correct I was just joking around but you
Know something about it, you know, you like you recognize something. Let's go Alex. Let's go Alex. Yeah, I can't wait to hear Alex's
This is gonna be fun. Hit it. Psycho Roni's
That's the emperors. I don't know who's this woman in your life. Yeah, you know, oh my baby
Really?
all the queens in the deck is emperors. It's like there's a really good or really a feminine
as long as it's not a progeny because that's one ugly bitch, but I'll take I'll take the emperors
card also, but then it's got king of water
talking about water paints they call I heard they call it water paints
you get the fire energy too. Do you know who I'm talking about, baby?
Juan's definitely like in like
what do we got?
said a castle
yes a castle, the king with the emperors, that's really good, the emperors coming towards the castle, okay
there we go, castle and emperors
that's card of the deck, the sun, the sun
it's the same card, that was the same castle
it's very similar, look, they are very similar
okay, that's the different one
day and night, it's like day and night a little bit, right, but it almost looks like the day and night of it
it's like, you got, it's a really good balance there
ooh, I like it
yeah, but the sun is like usually like the most positive card in the deck
the
it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it, it
Um, it reminds me kind of almost the the the eight of swords except this is like what you want protecting you
You've got like you've got the security system or something like that. Do you have any new security system or something?
We're terrible. One, two, three, four.
Another king and sword. We're getting another king and sword.
So this is like going to be able to like cut away what doesn't serve you in the situation.
Um, also this is like really good. Your mind is working really fast.
Um, uh, you're going to be able to figure something out really quickly.
And it's like another thing where it's like in front of this big, this big castle kind of thing.
So you're really protecting your property, like right here, like it seems, or it's like you're
preparing it for a woman or something like that. And another one, and this is Page of Pentacles.
So this is someone that's going to help you make some money too. But it's like, look,
another castle, this is like a lot of castles. And there's not like, I'm looking at this deck,
and it's not like all castles. And so I pulled like a bunch of...
the
Yeah
A lot of strength and something but this is like this is like you're really good with your money too right now
And this is like really
like um you're gonna be able to make the mula the mula there it is the unicorn that's really
how unicorns really can stand you see how they're content oh really look how happy almost like
your cat just content regal happy
Surrounded by abundance. There's one on top of it. Beautiful card. Beautiful. That's my favorite
But the moon right there it means that there's something still to be revealed like something that you're gonna find out on your own
That is like the moon above there, but there's
Protecting protecting something into that tree is someone in the tree though. Hold on. We got some
You have these beautiful trees though. Yeah, just like shelter. I see
of the
of of of of of of
All right
Are you dating are you with are you?
I can't I rather not talk about
I just see like maybe like there's like a special lady in your life. There is a special little mama
I know what's zip zip the point of life, but the lip. Okay. Maybe she won't slip
Maybe once and move in soon. I don't know. Okay. I don't know
Hopefully because I believe somebody somebody good. I think somebody's attracted to Alex right now
And it's I say I'm you right
What they call it blocking your blessings don't block your blessings Alex. Yeah
Baby, I'm blocking the
Lamp chop open down like a like a lamb
Somebody with a kid already like I don't know or like she's really into like a Maria teacher like a preschool
There you go. There you go. I love it. Yeah. Are you getting it? Jamie? Jamie? You want a reading? How are you, man?
Baby, where the hell have you been? Chanel?
We got to read it from Jamie. We got to read it from Jamie. Let's go psyche. She's back.
Disappeared and I see her in weird chats. I think I saw her in money. So I'm like, what the hell are you doing with your money?
She said, sure. I think she was having problems finding my chat. And so I think she did that. Oh, let's go. Let's give her a read and she's back.
Okay, well, we got this page of cups is coming up again. This is like like again. Why is she pinched?
It's like it's like this beautiful coming to like this piece inside of yourself or it's like
Yeah, but it's also it almost looks like a wand. He's holding right there
See it's like and this is see it's almost like with that steeple right there
And so maybe that's like almost like I've seen like it
Your church or something like that is like giving you some like some kind of support or emotional emotional strength right now
We got this we got a king of pentacles. This is like, you know
It could be a it could be a man with like it's some kind of good material stability
And but he's like waiting for you or he's looking for you and he's almost like I don't know
It's kind of like the way those hills look it kind of looks like boobs a little bit or I don't I don't know
I don't know. So someone's looking at you. Okay. This king of pentacles. He got some money. Okay
uh we got uh oh we got the queen of swords in your gemini i know you're a gemini so this queen
of swords this goes right into this gemini energy and it's like wow wow wow wow and you're going
down the hill like look he's like looking over that hill and you here you come down it right
so it's like i don't know who this guy is but he's like he's got some stability some really good
stability it's the man she's looking for she's looking for love so there is a man out there
Looking for the emperor and the money to represent. She got into a car accident recently. Maybe she's getting a big payday
This emperor energy too is like the emperor is like, you know
All the kings in the deck wars like the emperors all the queens in the deck, but I think this guy is like
Even better than you think even better than you thought it can be even better like that you know, we're thinking
Six of swords, okay
Yeah, okay, so and look at this there again. We have this like almost like a like a
merry-go-round merry-go-round
Energy and it's a sword's energy. Okay, and so this is like
Really?
You're told you open for lawsuits on my own
She's a millionaire, buddy. You're right on the money with a meeting or losses. Yeah
And it's like, this is like a big,
when I see the, I see this horse,
I see this victory coming through
to me for these lawsuits or whatever.
It's like, but again, the merry-go-round energy is like,
maybe it's been going around a lot too.
And justice, you just said the lawsuits, right?
And you got this justice, okay?
So you will be getting justice in this situation for sure.
But it's like, it's been just going around and around, right?
You know, quacks, little quacks just got all,
it's four lawsuits, huh?
I
Resonate it's a resonate let it resonate and then seven of ones. It's like you're really protected in the situation though
It's like yours yourself is protected
and
This looks like a son, too. It looks like you're really happy outcome for you
Higher fan something to do with this higher
It's, it's even higher than the law. It's like, it's like, it's, it's almost like a religious spiritual thing. Like it's something, something very positive.
And looking at this too, I almost see like, again, I almost like this pope is kind of dressed like the justice and it's like coming for you. Like he's like, he's usually facing facing the card, but he's like looking, and he's like waiting, but it's like, but it's coming, it's coming.
Okay, good. There we go. Hope you like that.
Love you, Jamie. Jamie's but Jamie was Jamie like it's so crazy like I everyone's been like almost everyone's been here
almost from the beginning like I like that's here like right now, but it's like but
It's like and look out like how far we've come together
But it's like look at how like things have like changed in a certain way like it's like
Things and more things change the more they say the same or something like that. It's like we're still like here
It's the same we've all gone involved progress, but it's like again
I get like this merry-go-round where it's like we all switched faces. We all switched we all switched switched
The energies and we're all coming full circle and stuff like that
I just feel like but I feel like we need to hold hands in a circle or something like that
I don't know
Well, you said
Poison DKG on this text you were the auto count
Give it to if not Chanel wants one
Eight of swords like okay, so okay, so I'm not
Not sure whoever wanted whoever called that out of this. This is this okay, so poison and say so
I think this is for Chanel Chanel. This is like the eight of swords
This is again like being trapped in your mind about something and like but it's like you just have to take out the blindfold
You're like you're worried about something. You're like you you're just overthinking something, but you really can get out of it
Okay, oh, and then you will because it's a ten of wands and this ten of wands
it's like uh this like really highly protected and like there's another I love this beautiful horse
right there it's like really really really protected and it's like you got this horse to
take you out take you out of something there's really there's really yeah there's really over there
yeah um
Yeah, over there. Okay. So, um, yeah, but it's like a lot of energy like a lot of there's a lot of energy in something
Okay, and then two of swords. So you have a blind spot in this, okay?
And you're at you're coming you're coming to the crossroads of the situation where it's like you're gonna be able to
Make progress finally you'll be able to be and you know, you're protected by these by the ten of wands, too
Um, Knight of Pentacles. I don't know if there's, I don't know who the man, there's a man or something like that.
Um, this is a really stable guy. He maybe is like a little bit.
Not I'll say he's just like he takes his time and stuff like that and it's like but he likes to stay at home
He doesn't like to like go like go running around and stuff like that, but he's like he's got a really
Nice home. He's got the little tower and he's like, you know
I just see him like coming kind of like trotting up and they are like Rapunzel now
I'm seeing like Rapunzel. He's like calling calling. You have to like let down your hair or something like that
Doesn't make me doesn't make sense, but I see like you're kind of in the tower
Like are you put it are you're like hiding away in the tower and you're waiting for this knight in shining armor?
He's coming this night of pentacles
Okay, a stability ace of swords. This is the truth. What you're hearing right now is the truth
Okay, you're gonna or you're really need the truth about something. I'll be able to put two more cards for you
We have this nine of cups. Okay. This is this is like this overflowing
happiness, but it's like almost like
You're almost
You've almost accomplished what you really want to accomplish. You want it you want because you want that 10 of cups you want that that
The big family and stuff around you and it's like
You've almost you've almost accomplished it. You just need you just need that one more. Just be careful
Don't leave your cups like behind unattended. Okay, and Queen of Cups. Okay, you've got this great
Arthos backstage Arthos backstage won't get a chance. He's not backstage, but yeah, you got this you got this energy
Yeah, but you got this
I'm not sure what your sign is but it's like you but you're really
Into your in control of your emotions and it's something to make you really really happy
You were like a reading. Okay. Not about you but a family member, of course ember. I got you
I hope you like that. I hope you like that um should now
Yes, okay about a family member. Is that all you want to say about it?
um or um because like I'm gonna start shuffling
um just tell me if you want to have a particular question about it or a particular person and uh
shuffling okay and I'll put Arthur up here here you go Arthur just wait a
second Arthur okay more specifically okay why are you accusing me of being a
lot now I'm kidding good morning good morning absolutely should know okay
good morning man he's in the middle of reading
I'm not sure if you had another question about that or more specific person you want to say, but oh, no, I think that's it
No, no, I'm talking to Amber once again. I'm gonna start. I'm gonna start it out Amber though. Okay. Oh, how's he gonna do recovery? Okay?
Okay, well we have okay. We have nine of swords like this is all this is like very
You know, okay, there's a lot of there's a lot of thought about it
There's a lot of people thinking about a lot of people worried about it
But I see like this protection about it like a very highly protected. Well taken care of okay
Best the best as best as you can like the best the best yes
Attention there and there's a ton of cups. There's gonna be happiness in this situation. There's gonna be a good
Nice. Yeah, this is for Amber. Just just hush a little bit or just okay. Sorry. Yeah, also like this is a really good
really good hospital, I think. I just see like a really, like, I just see like the best...
The best care like the it's like no matter what happens. It's like the bet like they're gonna get the best care and everything
It's like the best situation for them. Okay, and oh the star. Okay, so this is also like a looks like a really
well-protected area and and are they they're like popular in the hospital. I it's like
Or something like that there's like there's a there they're kind of known in there. They're like, they're like, oh, there's that you know that
that special patient that's a special patient okay hey Arthur shut the fuck up i'm doing
okay i'm gonna be myself sorry yeah okay um we have the hermit okay they're separated from the uh
they're separated from the regular population or something they're set apart i see set apart um
i don't know it's like i i see like that they're spending a lot of time
Maybe a loan, okay there. I don't know they're set apart there. Okay. I'm gonna I need a clarification there
Night of wands, okay
Yeah, they have a really people that are really really wanting to help really really wanting to help them and
If there's a problem they're rushing towards them, okay?
We get this little we get this like care card again. It's like this. They're really like they're really cared for just another cared for
Okay cared for and one more
And it's like
Okay, this is a page of cups. Okay again, it is like
They're okay. Yeah, he's loved. Yeah, I just see like he's getting a lot of attention and it's like this almost is like a
Seems like a scalpel or syringe. Okay to me. That's what it's like. It's like holding that that that
Like it's like it's like the best it's very surgical. It's very precise. It's very precise whatever whatever they need
I'm gonna pull one more
Okay, um, I don't know if it's something to do with the heart or something like that. Okay, but it's like
I'm just seeing like knives and stuff like that. So maybe there's gonna be some kind of surgery. Okay
Okay, I'm gonna pull one more. Okay. Oh
Okay
It's a new beginning. It's gonna be a new beginning. Okay, let me like learning how to reduce like learning something over again
Okay, it's the heart. Okay
Yeah, it's gonna be it, but I think I see this as a positive. It's gonna be a new start a new start for them
Okay, and I'm not exactly a
100% sure what that starts gonna be, but it's gonna be there. They're gonna be able to
Start over start over and so whether that's in this world or another world
I'm not 100% sure, but it's like they're
You know, and I wish you the best I wish was best for them. Okay?
You're gonna do a lot of things over, okay
Yeah, I see that's gonna be it's gonna. It's just like a new beginning. It's gonna be a new beginning
I think it's gonna be a good a good new beginning. Okay. It's gonna be good new beginning. Okay, I
See positive for that. So there you go
Hope you like that. Okay. Nice. Good morning chat. Good morning
Morning, well Arthur was holding that shit and he was about to explode bro. You lucky ended
of the
the
I could have corrected it in time,
but they decided to copyright strikes.
Now, the picture that I've been with Alexandra, I own, okay?
The picture with Abida and her fiance,
I don't know who owns that,
but they didn't take the picture,
and I don't think it's copy written.
And it was a privacy concern with Doxing,
that would have been a privacy strike.
And the third thing is that fair use
for anything else with the...
But I posted a little bit of all like 30 seconds of one of her programs.
I'm allowed, you're allowed to share a short thing with a person's program.
I mean, so they'll have to prove that they're in legal, in legal things.
But you know, Alexander's saying she's going to sue me for slander or whatever.
I'm not sure, but it's kind of sad situation.
I mean, it's like, and she also, what she did tonight, she was talking about.
I'm I'm trying to like get attention by saying I'm gonna I never said anything about I was going to
Unalive myself or anything that I said
some of the things they said to me seemed like it was like either very
Blase about that happening or
Encouraging and so but I'm not gonna say anything else because it was legal stuff with that right. Yeah
Yeah
It's very sad. We were just watching tonight and then we saw how close that was to be that we saw close
I was I mean, it's like I don't know how they turned against me so hard because really I
Was open to like trying to repair this for a long time and it's like
But I think at this point is just no going back. No, yeah either one
It's sad, but it's okay. I mean, it's like I'll be fine. I'll be fine. My channel. Yeah
No matter what my website my new cult codex dot me website or yeah, it will have a
Video player there. So whether I'm on twitch or kick or YouTube
It'll be people will be able to get notified when I go on the air
Yes, or get put on the mailing list and so hopefully people will follow me over there and stuff. Okay, yo
Um, I see it's like, I guess, a new chapter for you and you, you, you're revived.
You shaved.
I love it, man.
I love it.
Yeah.
I did shave because I was on, you know, Sam and they put me on like the show saying, oh,
look at how, how bad he looks now and how good he looked when he started.
I think I looked pretty much the same, except, you know, I was like a little bit like shaggy
here and like, you know, I, I, so I shaved a little bit tonight and put on a nicer shirt
maybe i'll take a little bit better care of myself but it wasn't because i was like you know
eating meth tacos or whatever they're trying to say it was because i've been under a lot of stress
and it's uh and it's not easy doing tacos. Someone said you're eating meth tacos that's a
hilarious. You know look at that. He was like he was doing meth not cocaine tacos so i mean
cocaine tacos i guess if you're eating meth tacos. But like i said it's like who's gonna go
I went to the pier, ate them on camera.
If I was so on meth, I would not be,
have it in an appetite for fish chocolate.
And the fish chocolates were good.
And then someone's on mercury poisoning
and all this kind of stuff.
I mean, it's like, it gets ridiculous.
and they're saying, oh, my Adam's apple looks like I have like five Adam's apples.
They have a picture of me like literally like eating like a burger.
They're like, look at him here.
And it's like, people are saying, oh, is he like, they're falling out in that picture.
And he has five Adam's apples.
And it's like, it's like, I mean, it's a little bit picking on me, I think.
I mean, it's like.
Hey, I'm not, I'm not, it's not, I'm not, they're like, oh, it's faces of meth and stuff.
Like, you know, that, that famous thing where that, that woman, her mug shots over the years,
and she, it's like, yeah, I don't think that's it. I think I still can be as good looking as I
was pretty much, maybe a little bit better or something like that, but.
Yeah, I know what I would you know what I think would suit you. What's up? I think like those high
Mail buns
Hey, we have a pony tail like a high pony tail. I couldn't find my rubber band. Hello
Hello. Hey, how are you?
Well, there's this one and you put the banner up who the fuck is I know her
Okay, okay, I remember to remember to bro
Could be a nice little cock. He showed his vagina tonight, and we didn't expect that but
I mean, he's right. You probably because a lot of people would join with my name knowing that I'm a trusted joiner, but
I just had a feeling I had a second hi Amber. What do you want dude? I don't have my like
Streamyard premium right now. So I can't put the nicer banner up. I have to put like, you know, it's like harder
I'm a little bit drunk right now. So so but another thing you can do is win
When their square is like down below you can click the three dots
Yeah, and obviously there's some of us that still have to fuck around but usually people that are joining under fake no like
Like down below right now
If you were to click on the three dots on my square. Oh, it's your name. I see your name. You see where
Yeah, yeah authenticated. Yeah, I think I think she wants to start a porn company with me. I remember Amber
Yeah, is it called like farting in the tub?
All right, that's something like that.
Exactly. Alex is only five.
Thanks for calling. Thank you.
Yeah, you know
No, I'm just say it, you know
My god, you ran you over like a little bitch
I ran him. I ran him off. Yeah, I do that. Wait, you're in the wrong person. Oh
Arthur was a little late. Not easy
Like that. I'm like, oh
Quack, you see what I think
That's quite
Look at the picture, bro. It's all there with the feet
Oh
You feel funny
That's one of my favorite movies on earth. Yes, I was a duck so weird
I still have shit like a fifth grade. He brought us people
It was weird it was good and weird bro, that's stupid white duck
I've heard of it.
That was acid all day.
You need acid to wash it like that.
There's a sexy duck.
Like the sexy duck woman I'm just kidding right now.
Like a...
Our duck.
Yeah.
That was my shit for like six months of my life
when I was small.
It was George Lucas, but Howard the duck was fucking scary looking. I'll show you what it's like. Yeah, look at it
But he's a hero. We loved him. He wasn't scary to us back then. He was like our hero. Yeah
What the fuck was the point in the movie and Howard the duck was the plot what the mission it said the movies about
and
Yeah, there's an alien threat, but he yeah, he came down to it was like short circuit, right?
Remember short circuit. Great. That was great. That was about the robot that like, you know
Johnny five is alive. I was like almost like an AI kind of thing. Like we're the I felt like I'm sheltered because I don't remember these
80s baby ever. Yeah, I'm old. I'm 81. I so it's like all right. How are the duck I can give you a pass on but
Short circuit no way
Short circuit was about why when were you born a robot that went rogue and thought it was alive. It's a amazing movie
Top three top five top five. Maybe I have seen it, and I just don't realize that I've seen it
Do you recognize this robot Nova, that's what he looked like right there. He had like a little those wheels right?
Oh, that's Johnny five. That's Johnny five. Johnny five
Yeah, they fell in love Stephanie Stephanie
Yeah, it's Stephanie Speck, Allie Sheedy, it says a sci-fi comedy about a military robot number five that gains sentience after being struck by lightning and escapes its creators, befriending an animal lover.
It's Stephanie Speck while being pursued by its designers, Steve Gutenberg and Fisher Stevens in the military.
The film follows the robot's journey of discovery.
Oh my goodness, my friend!
And you managed to avoid being decommissioned, right?
Oh, we have another guest.
Hold on.
I mean, look at the name with the banner up, bro, before it's the night in the sky. Okay, he's authenticated.
Yeah, money for 20 is cool. Money, money, money.
I didn't know him. Where do you come from? I know him. Amber, you watch this guy?
I know that he's not going to porn bomb. I would never do that. Okay, okay. I believe you.
I
Like I always think I'm like no manumurals like he used to join these panels before I know he go
I know he's
20 I think I heard of them once or twice. I don't know
Money for 20 is my brother
No, I was gonna say I'm pretty sure he's from this fucking panel
I just knew he wasn't gonna porn bomb, that's all I mean
The most I do I turn on my camera so cigarettes weed that's about it bro
I fucking got gifted a membership to your channel
So much check it out. Yeah, well actually it's a really I think I mean I think it's like a really
he does a really good panel because he's so laid back but he has like some like he is that he is
that guy in the bicycle who's that guy in the bicycle with the bike shorts yeah I mean it's
Harry Harry satsikas
I just heard people like just just like try to like say oh money
You know don't block me
I remember when everyone tell me what to do on the panel and stuff and money's and money's like, you know
So they back that he's he's getting good at uh, like, you know, hey, shut up
Bro
I'm surprised it went good. I didn't get no complaints
Yeah, money's a good guy
Really good show and yeah, I there's so there's so few people that actually do panels like you know, it is hard
I mean people get burnt out from them because it's like I mean
They can be hard in this community and stuff like that, you know, you see what I've been through you see as I see a lot of myself
and him like when I started out and it's just like
Everyone yeah, yeah, it's like see I've done it so much that I learned my lesson even trying to like help people because
because
It's so easy to be influenced by the wrong people. I just don't even waste my time
If you'll notice how I just kind of like let it play out and then after so long come in and just know that like I told you
So type shit
It's not that I like don't waste my time anymore trying to help people, but it's just
Unfortunately like streaming and running a panel is something you're just gonna have to figure out on your own because you're gonna like your own
boundaries your own like rules your own
It's like an initiation. It's like you have to go like everyone has to go through there
Taking down right you taking down. I've had that
Down I have in my mind number four number four. I gotta take it
But it's like now it's back. I've survived all these things. We have another
But yeah, I want to know why I've never had it taken down before
Why I'm a one and done person
If you come on my panel and repeat and say the n-word you're not getting on my panel ever again
I don't care if I'm cool with you and other
Sick showed his little dick tonight. You're reminding me
I saw it and that's another thing
Yeah
He poem bomb psyche with his own once it's little pecker. You want to hear easy, but psyche
You knew he I couldn't I know I think I don't know. So why did you let him on?
I got the pecker. I'm ready to go. I know I knew but I also know that I'll never get into a full moment
I delete it right away and I like you're basically yes, you still can
Well, I've just been lucky. I've been a problem over a hundred. Oh, no. Yeah, and so I mean it's like I've been porn bombed
And they're still up on the channel like I understand but why did you let him on though knowing?
Don't they don't care
He doesn't care and he like he and many said they tried to tell me I told you about this
I got poor mom earlier today too by someone with you someone using Natalie's photo and then I then
Yeah, but don't you think there's a difference between he could have poem bombed you with a cockpit
Like I do like a nice in his car to get up and put on your pants and show your own little people
That's crazy
That's a whole different level of crazy wanted me to see his dick. I think he's gay
But it was more of a vagina really. I mean, I was like, I don't know if there's anything there to like
He's probably a grower, not a short.
would be bigger than i'm not defending him like it looked pretty small but i'm just saying like it
could be a grower not a show i basically have like i've almost like you know i've given myself
warnings and stuff like that i've played music sometimes did you just hear this this core bag
from health it could be a grower this bitch has seen one inch cock grow into ten inch cock haven't you
I've seen it like a to do it like a cheer pet, right?
She grows literally it could be a girl. Is that we just like call it like yeah, I call like magic tricks
Penis have you ever seen puppetry of the penis have you heard of that like Davis? Yes
I love that shit. They could do like cheeseburgers and shit like that. Yeah, they make all these things. Yeah, I want to see
Yeah, Alex, can you send me some photos of you?
That'd be great. It's not as easy as you think it is. But yeah, I've seen it
Literally they took their two Nelsacks and then folded their penis in like a circle and then wrapped one
On the bottom and one on the bottom and it looked like this is for a cockpick
Yo, big mac is one thing my boy
Cockpick, am I hearing things?
Yeah
It's cockpock exactly Alice. Can you set me what I almost just jumped through a phone and choked up to death?
I almost jumped through a phone and choked his moves to the death rope. Don't ever say that to me again, brother
That will never happen in a million years
I mean, this is psyche. This is when you come in and play that
By the way, I will never come back up here because I will lose the cold complete respect for you
That guy just poem bombed you for the 900 times and I saw it myself
He showed his little dick if I ever come on this panel and see say go up here. I
Lose complete respect for you, and I'm out of here. I do not hang out with losers like that
So forever. I mean forever, bro
Oh, if I ever see big up here, you can lose I'll send the McQueen if you the same boy
Let me tell you
And I'm not lying or being a bait.
So give me a tomato.
I will never come back on the spot if I see that guy or
anywhere on Earth.
If he comes up to talk to us, he's gone.
That was the most disgusting retarded shit I've ever seen in my life.
If you ever
You lose my respect and I will not come back up here. I have no respect for no anybody that let's say
No, 66 on their panel
Alex ready ready you gotta worry about
I don't give a fuck bro. Did you see that shit?
If I see say go Peter moral they go with a stupid hat
Psyche laughing like it's all good. Nah, bro. Respect is done. I go left you go right
Because that's crazy
You got to have to expect for yourself at one point my friend
That's that was the most disgusting thing imagine that imagine that
Still I need that goes for everybody up here
Be it up. If I see signal, I'll never check you again. Oh summer if I see signal on your panel
I will never check you again money for 20 signal. It's on your panel
I will never check you again. Let's run in New York. If signals around your panel
I will never check you again. This goes out for the whole YouTube community
Alex
Alex nothing. How did it how did it go from him asking you for a cockpit to say?
I'm gonna fuck ask me for a cough
Suck a cockpocketry
Cockpocketry now he wants a cockpick. He makes fun of that shit. You think that's funny. That's disgusting. That's not funny to me
I don't know you you're getting torn bomb and laughing about it. That's not funny
We don't find that you're funny bro
Especially when it's a real person a picture maybe a picture. Maybe we'll let that slide
I'm sorry. I was fucked up. I put I threw a picture of a cock
But when you actually show your little pee pee like I witnessed tonight from signal
That signal to me is dead in my book. I I don't ever want to see that cat in my life
Have you anywhere like that's it. I'm done. Okay. I'm not gonna lie
I know I've known sick for a long time and that really shocked me. I didn't know he did that
That's disgusting and he's dead in my book for me and anyone else that hangs out with him is dead in my book
You understand
If he is with you if you let him bone your panel after what I witnessed tonight, you're dead to me
complete that to me
Literally
None of you
Sike, where'd you go?
It's did he leave because you were chewing him out. No, you gotta say the magic words
That's exactly where he left he's crying right now because he's hurting because he wants to let signal back because he's a freak like that
You gotta set boundaries, bro, I'm drawing a line in the sand
Well, he needs to come back
And let's came up and say what up. He's crying bro. He's crying this morning
He's mourning right now. Like oh my god. No, she's taking it again or no Alex me. Yeah
So he's crying right now. He's mourning
He's trying to wrap it around his mind that I told them if I was he signal on here
You'll never see me. He's trying to wrap that shit around his mind right now. That's where he left Amber. He'll be back though
All right, yes, I'm eating sorry
It's my after work snack
Bro
Hi classy, how are you?
Unless that's what you gave fucks do behind the stage show each other little pee-pee to each other
Okay, that's normal to them. No, no, maybe that's normal to them. Honestly, isn't there?
So that's normal. Let me know bro because I want no part of that. Listen bullshit. I have a serious I have a serious question
Isn't there a clip? What could you policy have a serious question? Let me hear this bullshit question
This is not a serious question bitch. I promise you. It's a serious. It's a serious one. Don't call me what I don't know
The fuck you are. I don't listen. You're a bitch. What about it?
You might have a lot of say over a second. Just a fuck off. You already lost me. I don't want to hear your question
End of story save it for another motherfucker. I don't want to hear your question. You like that you
I don't care. I'm not answering it. So too bad. You're talking and all this
And I'm not answering it on question
You want I'm not answering
I'm still gonna ask it. Don't answer me. You don't have to answer it. Let me ask it
How about this in there? Bye. I'll see you tomorrow, bitch. Oh
Okay, well, I just gonna point out the fact that there was like a clip of Lake
him talking about like pulling the psyche out of a car and fucking in the
shed of him in the bushes but she's like mad about like all this gay stuff like
I don't understand like it's psyche is channeled into the day like I'm not here
to kiss your ass nobody else's ass like
Like that's you know, there are boundaries there are boundaries of not letting someone else tell you what to do like no
I wouldn't let stick on my fucking panel after he fucking bought me like that
But I'm not gonna sit there and let someone else fucking tell me how to run my panel like holy shit
Especially when you yourself have made gay ass comments like that before like I don't understand that shit
What class scene
I'm not trying to trigger him, but I'm not I'm not here to suck nobody's dick either like I'm not
Like what's up?
It is funny Amanda and but that's all I was gonna ask him was like why are you like all gung-ho on like
The funny comment. Okay, so this is what happened like
Psyche brought up cock puppetry, which is like a thing that cock puppetry is the thing
There's like a whole ass show like in Vegas or some shit where dudes will take their penis and like
Make shapes and shit out of their cocks
Whatever and then so Psyche made a comment of like hey
Alex send me a picture of your cock puppetry or some something like that
And then all of a sudden Alex started just going off about SIG and I'm like I was trying to like make the connection like where
Why are you all of a sudden going off about SIG?
And then then I was gonna say hey like I don't understand why you
Are saying all this shit about gay people when you yourself as a clip of you literally talking about pulling psyche out of his car
If you were a cop and raping him in the bushes like I don't understand that so that like he's talking about losing respect for people
Because it's it's fucking it's psyche's channel. It's his panel. He can let sit up here
Every fucking night if he wants and he can get porn bomb every fucking night if he wants it's his fucking channel
like
And and and psyche seems to be doing pretty damn good like I mean he's got a lot of subs his channel's growing fast
Like he's got a lot of haters, but that's what happens when you get a channel growing like
So crack on life. Oh my god, Brittany
It is satire. It's I mean, I don't know about I mean, I guess you'd call it satire
Because it's for like the shits and giggles type shit, but
Hey, Amber. Yeah, I'm sorry. I was just kidding with him and it's like but he's being so loud
You know, please came over here the night
There's like seven cops here and like because I was because I was being too loud or something like that but
He was I don't he gets mad at me. It's like I was just kidding Alex
But I don't even think he realized what you asked like I understand that it could be coming from like a good place
But at the end of the day
It's your channel. You can be porn bombed every day if you want
You're the one who has to do the work and building it up and doing all the whatever crazy shit you do like
Yeah, I don't you know
Oh, no, some random ass dude that has the name of a gay ass fucking designer in New York City is gonna be
You know, oh, no, he's gonna you're gonna lose his respect because you let you know a well-known fucking panel guest on your channel like fuck him, bro
Well, yeah, but he is I mean I'll say he's really good to me like you know like not a lot of people like really like
You know help me out anymore, and he has helped me out a lot, and I mean I like I just don't know why he gets
It's like so I'm glad you like him
But does he manipulate you and tell you what to do on your own channel, or does it give you good advice?
Um, I you know there's a difference. Yeah, he does he helps me here does how he does
He is I think he does at the end of the day. He's been here for a long time
He really cares about me and cares about the channel. I mean, he's actually accidentally formed on cool. Well, cool. Fuck who bitch?
Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker. Fuck you motherfucker
One at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a time, one at a
Psyche is not gonna lose me over any of you remember that that's number one
Number two and say it's come ever comes up your side. I'm gone. You'll never see me again
I promise you. I don't want to be around that motherfucker ever on any panel
It's associated with so it's taking those 60 things ever comes on your panel
forever. Yeah. Why? Yeah. How many times a thing about him?
McDonald's? What do you say to you? What do you say to
you? I don't give a fuck when you have to say psyche signal
comes on this panel again. You'll never see Alex again. So
think about that. Think about that, brother. And I'm not
threatening you.
i'm telling you a fucking fact i don't want to be around that bullshit i don't play that i don't
want to be around your little kitty fucking freaks that put updates on live panels i don't want to
be around that bro a part of that you never did that to me i've never seen that appear by anybody
and that's the first time and the last time i'm gonna see that if i see that again if i see signal
Good. Let's go. There's someone else backstage. Let's go. Let's go. Oh, it's. Okay. It's
Arthur. Alex. Good morning. Alex. That's great. That's great. And he hella defend
you, but just calm down. Amber. Amber. How you like that, bitch? Shall you stupid crack
him up? No two having bitch.
If I see signal up here again, I'm gone and the story
Like he's ass like he's ass all of a sudden what happens? I'm not kissing like he's ass. Oh my god
Yeah, it's fucking asshole. What are you talking about?
That was the most disrespectful disgusting thing I've ever seen in my life, and I will not stand for that
I don't want to be around that
You understand psyche you put me through that by allowing that loser up here to do
that you owe me psyche for like the torture I endured from that he's crying you understand
you have signal 66 convoked here there is no outside the McQueen for you ever again
whatever that means to you I don't know if you don't give a fuck whatever but I'm telling you
and the story
they're breaking up and sick comes on yes look how stressed out he is I just want
to clarify I don't suck anybody's asshole you better not never dirty that's
fucking amber bro I come up be doing that I come on I don't
I
Fucking what a loser
To get a whore a fucking retard and some potato chip loser up here and some guy that pulls out a stick on the panel
Yo, psyche, you ever put me through that shit again after all the shit bro, we've been through if you ever make me go through that again, my man
You understand that was some fucked up shit.
Wow.
You're strong.
You like that?
That's funny to you, bro.
Why are you going to lose your chance?
That's funny?
That's all your panel, bro.
You Peter, get it?
That was the most disgusting thing I've ever seen.
You have to get a backup channel to the back.
Don't ever tell me you like that.
I didn't say I like that.
I'm a quack.
Oh my god.
Quick, get him to yell, Alex.
Let him speak.
What's the matter, bro?
What did you do?
You didn't suck his dick today or something?
What's going on?
OK.
SIG porn bombed psyche earlier
What and Alex is still raging about it. Oh because it's not
Finish the story. He pumped up with his own dick. He pulled his pants down and showed his own dick and labeled it. Yeah
I'm never going to do that again
If I will see that piece of shit up here, I'm gone, bro.
I'm on Alex's side.
Ghosts of fucking Amber State for McDonald's.
He's right.
Ghosts of Amber State for McDonald's every night, motherfucker.
If I will see that piece of shit up here, I'm gone.
Alex is right. Alex is right. Alex is right.
I didn't say to let's say that.
Pardon me Alex. I love you to death home, but can you please stop screaming? Yeah, can you please Alex please?
Yeah, stop screaming when people stop showing their dicks up here
That was the most disgusting
Like, you listen to him, this hooker bitch, Amber, you hooker bitch, get the fuck out of here, go smoke some crack, you dumb bitch.
I
Show me a clip of where I said
Show me a clip of where I told him.
Send me a clip.
I don't agree with SIG doing it at all, but he does it all the time, and I don't know why you let him up.
And that's what I said. I said, why would you have somebody on that you know poised on somebody earlier in the day?
Okay, so let me clip me.
Show me a clip of where I said to let SIG on panel.
Show me a clip of where I said that.
I'm going to send a question.
The sick have a little penis.
Yes.
I don't know.
Wow.
I've never seen it.
Amber, does he have a little penis?
He has a little penis, yes.
Very small.
That's why he tries to overcompensate.
Yeah, so now because I didn't tell you I had to tell to let sit on your panel
See, and that's the point, like...
that's the point I was saying earlier is to let somebody like this come on your
panel and just tell everybody what to do and threaten them and all that shit like
I'm not gonna be I'm not gonna be I'm actually some psyche a nice amount of
money I didn't say I didn't I didn't I didn't say I did
No, no, no, I didn't say I did, but I think it's crazy that someone should be afraid to
have an opinion because someone else is going to threaten to call CPS on their child.
Go ahead, it will be 100% unfounded, go ahead, do what you need to do.
Do what you need to do. Arthur, you're just getting a hard on right now because Alex is
attacking me, but you're never gonna see that again. Alex is just on a, Alex is in a psychosis
right now and hearing whatever the fuck he wants to hear. Well, and I'm just waiting for a clip
of where I told Psyche to let Sig on panel.
Because that's what he's raging about.
He's saying that I said to let SIG on panel.
I never said to let SIG on panel.
not not once did I say that
well I'm the only mandated reporter on this panel right now and nobody's calling CPS
I appreciate that and I'm actually a mandated reporter as well
I work in the recovery field and I'm actually a peer support specialist
well I'm medically retired from teaching but I still have a license
Are you married, Jay?
Who is this?
Her name's Amanda.
Holly qualified in my field, by the way.
Amanda, who does Amanda?
And that's awesome.
Like, I shouldn't be as scared to have an opinion.
Not once did I say formula.
No, not at all.
Not at all.
I even said why would you have someone on panel.
Author, it's because I'm on other panels. I come over here to site sometimes because I enjoy site.
But aren't you the one that has a channel on TROLA? Isn't that you?
No, not at all. I don't have. I'm not a content creator.
She sounds like INX, but it's not INX.
Yes, INX, yes.
Yeah, you can look at my channel.
I don't have any content of it.
So exactly like INX, wow.
No, I know a little.
There's quite a bit of difference, but...
I know who that is, but you know, I...
She sounds like her, yes.
Yeah, and it's like...
Oh, classy thought to Sandy.
You would have stopped and I don't like threatening Alex like no and I don't want to have sick
back up anymore.
I don't know why you thought I said that or she said that wasn't poison.
She was saying don't have them on because I should have known about it.
Yeah, I was saying that.
I was just saying don't be manipulated is all I say.
Hey, um, pardon me.
I'm away from my phone.
Can you mute me real quick?
I need to do something in the kitchen.
It's going to be loud.
Thank you.
Poison.
Poison, please let me know where I said to let's stick on panel.
Yeah, she did it. She did it. I think I just said like I made a stupid joke about puppetry the penis and I don't know
What how it got all crazy and stuff? I'm sorry, Amber
like and
Alex you just take a deep breath and they listen because you're not like I mean yeah, he went into a rage
and uh sorry the last thing i want to do is lose you a big supporter and like i'll totally out of
respect leave if that's what it takes but i was just merely having an opinion i can't have a question
nobody asked if you already you always want me to leave you know arthur you're only nice to me
when you see my cleavage like you're mean and then you see my cleavage and then you're nice
and then after a while of not seeing my cleavage like you're mean again
Anything else so I got a question for you. What's up, and I want you to be honest. Yes
What's the question? All right. I know you're gay, right? You're obviously gay. Yeah, okay
After seeing six wee-wee did it turn you on?
Not in like the least bit in a million years. It was like
It was like a vagina, I mean, it's like, no, I would rather I'd rather a real woman's vagina than an inside out penis
I mean it was sad and we saw like you guys see the thumbnail for the show tonight
It's like that is Stig's real face. He is like a miserable
I mean, I've had him on for like a year and it's like this guy's really got an old because it's like now
He's like he's like he's harps on me. He's like and I got porn bombed earlier by Natalie's picture
Thank you, Cassie. He said oh, hi man. Lola. He said oh
I told you I've been trying to tell you how to like and then he porn mom. It's always like yeah
I should have known better. I should know okay. So yeah, you should have and like I just said in chat like I like sick
Do I agree with a lot of what he says and does?
Absolutely not.
I don't let him on my panels because I know what he does and what he says.
But do I hate him? No.
Am I going to let someone else tell me that I can't have him on my panel?
No, but I'm not going to have him on my panel for my own boundaries.
Yeah, and I think that's a good idea, like from now on, I think I should.
He's going to porn.
He's going to porn bomb you as soon as you're not paying attention, obviously.
Was he drunk or something? Like what happened?
I don't know.
He's always drunk.
He was doing shots of alcohol,
but he's pouring bomb somebody earlier today
when he wasn't supposed to be drunk.
So I don't know, he seems like he's-
But he's always drinking.
If he's on panel, he's drinking.
I mean, so lose to him for being confident
with his little penis.
I don't think it has anything to do with confidence.
I mean, at that point.
I don't think so.
No, I think it's more like a shock factor.
I think Tommy James is confident to go like, you know,
harass the lady at the bed store
where there's nobody even in the store, you know?
Wait, hold on, you don't like Tommy James?
I don't mind Tommy James, but he like went and he asked the guy at the butcher counter
and said that the fish smelled like his ex-girlfriend's vagina, and he embarrassed everybody, and, uh...
Oh, I know what you mean.
That was terrible.
You were kind of like secondhand embarrassed by him.
Oh, yeah.
Thank you, Jimmy. It's not my fault.
Everyone was hey, I mean it's like hey, but I think my I'm really excited tonight because it's like no matter what what's wrong
Like the channel whatever the channel survives and everything. I've made it through and I have a new website and like whatever
Platform I'm on it all be streaming from the website, and I hope everyone
Stays with me. I mean I've had enough problems that with people like you know that I thought were friends and stuff like that that
Turned on me and stuff. So it's like really
Like everyone stays with me means a lot to me and so I don't want. Yes
Well, I don't know where I want
He says what I want and say what I want see
His plan you played right this six way to go sick
Now yes, it's gonna be called on me because of you sick. What Arthur?
I mean, you're allowed to porn bomb with your tits. We're all welcome to that. So oh my god
Thank you. No, you're you're banned from the show and you can
You can just like thank you Arthur. I appreciate that. I'm not gonna be stupid enough to
Everyone's just gonna think I'm stupid. Is that what you want? You just want everyone to think I'm stupid
And if you let him up, you would look like a dumbass. Yes. Yeah, and so I'm gonna ban and as I said, I'd like to sit
He's bad. I would let him on my panel will wickers or whatever his real name is banned
Okay, so he's not coming up anymore. Okay, that is definitely not his name. He's fucking Mexican this shit
who
Cig, the name is probably like George Jose.
I don't think he's Mexican.
I feel like he's more Native American.
I thought he was kind of Guatemalan.
I'm not sure.
No, he's like a native Mexican.
He's like a Aztec.
That's possible.
He looks like one of those, like,
Mayori, like, stone face, you know, those,
those, you know, stone face, like.
No, you've seen that movie Apocalypto?
Yeah.
You've seen that movie Apocalypto?
It's basically, what do you want to say?
No, it won't be safe.
He does not.
I mean, from what we saw, he's really small penis, but like I said, he could be a grower,
not a shawar.
But it looks really small.
Do you like your, do you like the thumbnail, Sig?
We have a big nose.
Your nose is bigger than your penis, you know that?
Well, it's like, I think you should change that
because I think he's gonna copyright you or something.
Well, you know, he's gonna have to copyright Dex,
his friend Dex.
He'll have to copyright his friend Dex
if he wants to do that,
because Dex is gonna have to despise him,
not on Sig.
I think Dex-
No, he could still get you for privacy,
but it wouldn't be horrible.
Yeah, and that's the appropriate way,
is like a privacy thing,
is like they gave you two days to take it down, right?
um like that's why Alexander um striking me for privacy but they struck me for copyright
on stuff like that so there you go hey perry page perry page is here we're behaving we're taking a
deep breath and alex he's he's banned from the studio i'm not gonna let him on again and guys
he had a he had a decision i'm not gonna oh pages or not and he did and so
Who do you... Who else do you follow?
Yeah, that sucks, Chibi.
I couldn't really tell if he was cut or uncut.
It kind of went by.
So here's the deal.
It looked like it was my.
I had the chat screen open, so half the screen was covered.
But then when I looked up, I could see his Zephupa.
And they're shaking, so I knew what he was doing.
Yo, no homo.
I got to see this.
No homo.
OK, you can go to my Discord.
Arthur, you're my Discord.
I'll send you a picture, OK?
All right.
I definitely don't want to see it.
You don't want to see an Amanda?
I haven't used to see it.
I'll post it in the discord.
I mean, I'll send it to you, but actually, I don't want to get this.
I mean, it's kind of homo.
It's not the, I have a penis myself, so it's not gay.
How big is it, Arthur?
That's like, I could probably tell you it's bigger than six at this point.
Yeah.
I'm sure.
Well, that's, yeah.
That's not.
I mean, prove it.
I mean, Alex, he gets his way when he gets drunk.
Yeah.
I know it comes from like a good place, but damn he went nuts. Oh, and like I'm not gonna be afraid to have my own opinion about something
And I'm sorry that Alex misunderstood what I was saying, but he went a little schizo
The music is what I was saying too, but Arthur the pictures on its way. Okay. All right. Thank you
But cock cock puppetry is really a thing and I think it's fascinating that dudes can twist their penises into those
Cute little New York Broadway show. I think it's on Broadway, right? It's always like a yeah
Yeah, and like have you guys ever heard of the wall of vaginas? It's like this museum of of
Vaginas shapes like all like there's a bunch of different like women's
It's cool. It's like trees that have like the trees look like a vaginas and stuff like here's you see those awesome
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, they're pretty cool
So I'm I don't know I think I'm fascinated by you know the human body and stuff like that. So yeah amber type
Are you gonna chime me out if I type in chat Alex?
No
Yes, you will watch you
Welcome to he's welcome to
Alex is managing mod he can time out mods
Okay, well
Alex don't time her out. Okay. You don't have permission for that. Okay, just just it's okay
You know what? I'm I'm gonna do what Alex does and I'm gonna push buttons. So don't get mad at Alex for doing this
I'm gonna get mad at Alex for doing this
I'm not gonna hate you because your rogue mod, but I'm gonna type in chat just to say I'm typing in chat
Okay. Hey Arthur. I sent you the picture. You can see it. Thank you. It looks disgusting
Anybody else want it in this for the record, but he better not ban me. It's not gay. I look at vaginas and I'm not gay
Thank you. I'll just hide it
I need to chat and she can't do okay, Alex. I
Typed into Alex. We're gonna have to take you to just a standard mob tonight. We can talk about it later
Okay, just you're going a little bit wild. You can't can't handle it Alex now
I'm getting reports long to that. I don't want him to get mad at you. He's not gonna get mad
I mean, it's like as long as he as long as he doesn't ban me. I
Won't cry about it. I'm just gonna take you to manage and to standard mod Alex cuz you're going crazy in the chat
Okay, he said no, but who you hide it. He's trying to amber for we time down for 10 seconds. Okay, so you're fine
Okay, I can handle that. I can handle that
I can handle 10 seconds and he timed out case class a classy PB is classy PB. Okay?
Oh, you didn't turn out classy because classy was defending me now. You're gonna piss me off Alex
Get the fuck over it and get up here Alex and stop taking it on people that defend me
But I know class. We didn't say anything to deserve it. So you show the fuck out
Alex stop it stop it Alex, okay
Tell me how everybody stop it Alex. I'm gonna I'm gonna I could I don't want to you know, I love you Alex
Take it away. Come on poison. What are you uploading?
There we go
You're okay. I think I got everybody everybody back. Okay, and Jamie. Oh, he's he's uploading the penis
Yeah, did you see it? Did you see it on Arthur? I
Don't know if that's the real Aldi we'll find out. Oh, it's Aldi here. Yeah, but Aldi Aldi be nice
Aldi you want to come up Aldi Aldi's porn bomb me. I think home, but then don't
He's gonna do it again. All the I've seen all I've seen all the I've seen your balls
Are you in your own thing? Everybody's doing all these balls. No sig is on Aldi's team. Get it, right?
Okay, sig is on Aldi's Aldi
Sing is Aldi
Like I mean it's like I can like and I mean I'll be able to get in time, but I don't I don't want
Problems, okay. Don't cause problems with me and and Alexander McQueen. Okay. He Alexander said you I'm not trying to
Hold on Google said he's gonna take it down who said I'll upload it to your channel. Okay. No poison
He's just now looking at he's just now looking at
Was it a video or a picture?
I see I didn't get a look at it long enough to even have a fair judgment. Are you on my discord? I could send it to you on the discord if you want.
Okay, thank you Amanda. I'm sorry that you thought that I was on
SIG side, but I'm not on porn bombing side. Just so you know
Well, now we know why like SIG is such it's so it's so sad though. I'm mad at the world
I mean, it's like I would be too if that was in my pants, you know SIG this comes from like
I think it's more like a shock factor. I don't I really don't think he's and I'm not defending him
I'm just saying I don't think he's doing it was like the malicious intent like ruining your channel
I just think he comes from like the internet era where like
Doing that kind of shit. I mean, it's like it's like it looks like it looks like I got a baby ant eater
I'm so fucking sad. Yeah
Sig that's not good
Oh my god, and he's fat. Oh my god. He's just so fat. Oh
Let me see. I think I think sick actually the I think I saw like on rumble like that. He was like a they had like some kind of funny
Clip in it like on trip kick on
Let's see if I can find it real quick
Maybe this is a CO plastic surgeon
Sick it's okay, you know, it's like but why would you show that?
Like because now I mean I've been embarrassed before but that's really
Alex, get over it. I'm not a traitor. Just get up here and fucking join. Just, you know, learn to handle someone who might have a differing opinion than you.
But I never said for him to let sick join. I straight up said, why would you do that? Knowing he porn bombs somebody.
So get up here and join and have a fucking real conversation.
SIG going it says SIG wasted on ever clear doesn't hold back against Q45 or SIG goes up on Tommy
rather see
I like him going at Q45 to 45s effect. Okay. Look. We just I mean a second. Yeah, it says Tommy James Q and SIG
So this looks good. Hold on one second. Let me just get this up one second
He's got the link okay one second Alex, I'm an OG around here get up here and talk to me
Yeah, kind of a big deal be right there whoever is coming trying to come to the studio. I'll be right there. Okay, so oh
Here's clumsy. Oh three in glow. Don't you?
What up clumsy
No clumsy
Is it this another porn bomber you better not
Q is only by doing this he's only defending his own ego
It's not even about his mother because if it was about his mother
Then he would
Draw attention away from it. He would be trying to draw attention away from it
But instead he's pushing himself forward into it with his mother's name in vain
You know what I mean?
At the end of the day all you need is a black roommate
That's all you need for you. That's all it takes
I'm so ugly, but my mother isn't dead.
You're so cute.
I'm not old, mother.
I'm old.
You might be old.
And that's real.
I'm scared, but when this whole fucking community,
I'm an old dude.
So goddamn old.
Eat shit and choke and die on your own piss.
Oh my god.
How do you not kill yourself every day?
Jesus, I feel bad for you.
Short, ugly, fucking Mexican, Paul.
My god.
Uh-oh.
Smoking that nigga in the back.
Oh.
Sounds like you getting packed out again, Sing.
Remember this.
Oh, this dude literally has never felt a vagina.
I don't want to hear anything out of niggas
who have never gotten any pussy.
You literally eat date bitches.
I mean it, what happens?
Bro, he's got his phone out, he's getting ready to record when he turns off.
Shout out to your mother, I'm sure that she was a great person.
Lots of asses.
But you're making her look good, buddy.
Just be prepared, that's how people get used.
You're not making her look good!
What if you don't make anybody
Then make a few 45 cuz suck my whole dick
I'm not fucking friends with that nigga. I'm not kissing his ass. Oh, we're in the group chats. No, we're gonna make up fake drama
We're gonna make up fake conflict
Fuck out of here
He doesn't even know what he's talking about
Six not gonna be around